<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000705_0020" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Campbell v. State">Leah S. CAMPBELL v. STATE of Arkansas</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 94-1375</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">51 Ark. App. 147</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">912 S.W.2d 446</citation>
          <decisiondate>1995-12-20</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T18:17:46Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:34:13Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-18T10:47:40Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-18T10:48:18Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00085_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2bd5986818e9bbb67260c069324d9891" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="9300">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00085_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00085_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2f7aa50a4a5c786c01fdd8e2c5a3458c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="44354">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00085_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00086_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4d6b0c0edf4621eff08a940879344e1c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57732">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00086_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00086_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="79c83c12499817cea82332f9b6f4ef4b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="51380">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00086_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00087_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="86a2dd79b0a7c595c8c1807afa3bbaff" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="48834">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00087_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00087_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="fb324fb84c60d0bcce15c4c2701adced" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="45170">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00087_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00085_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="56a2b0f0ead0d1b2f6d3ed42970d10de" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1367549">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00085_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00085_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="5815865265693e7875e01662ea6a5bed" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2283160">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00085_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00086_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="076463a418040cfda3df35b9dc566b81" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2645656">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00086_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00086_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="b0c3fd34c5f9dd4e1d7e45d358a80384" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2629020">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00086_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00087_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4f0b9e3c39f9103783789122305e2607" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2599865">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00087_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00087_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cd455016efeb09a17fb37fed866cd5f5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2515742">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000705_00087_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00085_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="743534ba45a242b389ae3bcdba17ae45" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="8211">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00085_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00085_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7875147363ccf87696aec862d4edcd0c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="72509">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00085_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00086_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6bfacceaedad668362bd3c3680bec223" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="97707">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00086_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00086_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="93afc947a4dc9371cc40d521e0444787" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="88811">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00086_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00087_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="74b36a15e7523bedf3ab0366e942885b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="78773">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00087_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00087_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f9dd9bd766f637ce5c42de501c537b2c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="76847">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000705_redacted_ALTO_00087_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0020" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="147" lastpage="152">
              <court id="b169-4" pgmap="169">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber id="AnV" pgmap="169">CA 94-1375</docketnumber>
              <citation id="ARF" pgmap="169">912 S.W.2d 446</citation>
              <parties id="b169-3" pgmap="169">Leah S. CAMPBELL v. STATE of Arkansas</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b169-5" pgmap="169">Opinion delivered December 20, 1995</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b174-9" pgmap="174">Robbins, J., and Bullion, S.J., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b170-10" pgmap="170">William R. Simpson, Jr., Public Defender, by: C. Joseph Cordi, Jr., Deputy Public Defender, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b170-11" pgmap="170">Winston Bryant, Att’y Gen., by: Angela S. Jegley, Senior Asst. Att’y Gen., for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b170-12" pgmap="170">John E. Jennings, Chief Judge.</author>
                <p id="A6_" pgmap="170">This is an appeal from an order involuntarily committing the appellant to the Arkansas State Hospital for a forty-five day period. The sole argument raised on appeal is that there was insufficient evidence to support the probate court’s finding that appellant posed a clear and present danger to herself or others. We agree and reverse and dismiss.</p>
                <p id="b170-13" pgmap="170(207) 171(23)">On October 6, 1994, Mrs. Lyda Campbell filed a petition seeking the involuntary commitment of her daughter Leah Camp­bell for treatment of mental illness. Leah Campbell is a thirty-­six-year-old board-certified psychiatrist. The petition alleged that Dr. Campbell had “at least a four-year history of mental illness” and that on the 5th of October the manager of Forest Place, the apartment complex where Dr. Campbell lived, told the petitioner that Dr. Campbell had physically attacked a Terminix man who was spraying her apartment and “nearly pushed him off the sec­ond floor balcony.” The manager said that Dr. Campbell would have to move because it was her second assault, in that she had tried to attack a maintenance man two weeks earlier. The man­ager also complained that Dr. Campbell was walking about wear­ing only a bathrobe. The petition also alleged that Dr. Campbell had screamed that the petitioner was going to hell and slammed a door and refused a request from her father on the same date to get help. It said that Dr. Campbell had walked off two jobs since returning to Little Rock in August 1993 and was not getting care for her illness. The petition also alleged that she was dependent on her mother and father for support. The petition listed Mar­garet Raney, the manager of Forest Place, as an additional wit­ness.</p>
                <p id="b171-6" pgmap="171">On October 7, 1994, the Pulaski County Probate Court held a hearing to decide whether Dr. Campbell should be committed for a seven-day period for evaluation. Lyda Campbell testified that she and her husband saw their daughter on October 4 and asked her to get some treatment “because she was unemployed and had run out of money.” She testified that on October 5, Dr. Campbell was very rude to her parents and acted with hostility toward them. She testified that the statement about a four-year history of mental illness was based on what “mutual friends in New York” had told her.</p>
                <p id="b171-7" pgmap="171">Margaret Raney, the assistant manager at the apartment com­plex where Dr. Campbell lived, also testified. She said that on approximately September 14, 1994, Dr. Campbell came into her office upset because she had been to her bank to withdraw money to take a cruise and had been told her account only had $20.00 in it. Dr. Campbell told Ms. Raney that she felt like the bank manager was happy about not giving her the money. Ms. Raney testified that Dr. Campbell then lit a cigarette despite a sign on Ms. Raney’s desk that says, “Please, do not smoke.” When a gentleman who happened to be in the office, whom Ms. Raney described as a native American, called Dr. Campbell’s attention to the sign, she told him to “shut the blank up” and called him a “spic.” In the course of the conversation Dr. Campbell told Ms. Raney that she hated her parents and that “if it were not for prison, she would murder them O.J. Simpson style.” Ms. Raney testified that Dr. Campbell then got up and made some gestures that “mimicked a chimpanzee.” Ms. Raney said that Dr. Camp­bell seemed to be “a very upset lady on the edge.” Ms. Raney also testified that she had observed Dr. Campbell walk across the parking lot in her bathrobe without any undergarments.</p>
                <p id="b171-8" pgmap="171(69) 172(38)">Dr. Campbell testified that she acted with “some hostility” toward her parents because they came to her apartment to take her car away for the second time in the recent past. She testified that she was treated as an outpatient for depression about a year ago after she had returned to Little Rock. She testified that she could have made the statement that she would like to kill her parents because they “continually come over and provoke argu­ments with me and set up very frustrating situations.” She con­ceded that she had been outside in her bathrobe in the past when her cat had gotten out.</p>
                <p id="b172-6" pgmap="172">On this evidence the court ordered the involuntary com­mitment of Dr. Campbell for the purpose of a seven-day evalu­ation.</p>
                <p id="b172-7" pgmap="172">On October 14, 1994, the probate court held a second hear­ing. The only witness was Dr. Jarrod Adkisson, a second-year resident at the University of Arkansas for Medical Sciences, working as a psychiatrist for the Arkansas State Hospital. Dr. Adkisson testified that he had diagnosed Dr. Campbell as “bipo­lar, type II.” He testified that “type II”</p>
                <blockquote id="b172-8" pgmap="172">indicates that within the last two years there has been an episode of major depression, which did occur last year by her own report. That also implies that there aren’t a lot of specific criteria to meet what we would call a florid, grandiose, manic stage, that there are activities which we consider to be hypomanic, which in themselves would be some of the intrusiveness that she’s shown, from the impul-­sivity, some of the difficulties that she has shown both in her professional life and in her private life. It does meet the criteria for bipolar type disorder, but it’s a lesser diagno­sis, less severe — it’s not as severe a form of bipolar as the regular bipolar diagnosis.</blockquote>
                <p id="b172-9" pgmap="172">Dr. Adkisson testified that Dr. Campbell had shown some evidence of hostility toward staff and some evidence of “bizarre behavior.” He testified that she made the comment that she threw up her medication because the Italians made her do it. He testi­fied that “another night she got angry at staff and made a rather flippant remark that she might get out of here and kill some­body.” When asked about it the next day, “she said that she was upset and had gotten angry with the staff, but denied any [inten­tion] of wanting to hurt herself or anyone else.” Dr. Adkisson recommended that Dr. Campbell begin a trial treatment of the drug Lithium, but that she had refused to begin treatment. He testified that a drug screen was performed on appellant and that it was negative.</p>
                <p id="b173-5" pgmap="173">Finally, Dr. Adkisson testified repeatedly that Dr. Campbell was not currently a danger to herself or anyone else and that she did not require any further inpatient treatment. He testified that he believed she suffered from a “mood instability.”</p>
                <p id="b173-6" pgmap="173">After hearing the evidence the court stated that there was ample evidence to indicate Dr. Campbell suffered from a men­tal illness and needed some treatment. The order involuntarily committing Dr. Campbell for a forty-five day period stated that the court found by clear and convincing evidence that Dr. Camp­bell posed a clear and present danger to herself or others.</p>
                <p id="b173-7" pgmap="173">
                   The case at bar is moot in a sense because the forty-­five day commitment order has run its course. We nevertheless decide this case on its merits because this kind of proceeding will almost always become moot before the litigation can run its course and a decision here might avert future litigation. See Camp­bell v. State, 311 Ark. 641, 846 S.W.2d 639 (1993).</p>
                <p id="b173-8" pgmap="173">
                   In order to obtain a forty-five day commitment order the State bears the burden of proving by clear and convincing evidence that the person sought to be committed is a clear and present danger to himself or others. Ark. Code Ann. § 20-47-­214(b)(1)(A) (Repl. 1991). Arkansas Code Annotated section 20-­47-207(c) (Repl. 1991) provides:</p>
                <blockquote id="b173-9" pgmap="173">(c) INVOLUNTARY ADMISSION CRITERIA. A person shall be eligible for involuntary admission if he is in such mental condition as a result of mental illness disease or disorder that he poses a clear and present danger to him­self or others;</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b173-10" pgmap="173">(1) As used in this subsection, “a clear and present dan­ger to himself’ is established by demonstrating:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b173-11" pgmap="173">(C) The person’s behavior demonstrates that he so lacks the capacity to care for his own welfare that there is a reasonable probability of death, serious bodily injury, or serious physical or mental debilitation if admission is not ordered.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b173-12" pgmap="173(11) 174(43)">(2) As used in this subsection, “A clear and present dan­ger to others” is established by demonstrating that the per­son has inflicted, attempted to inflict, or threatened to inflict serious bodily harm on another, and there is a rea­sonable probability that such conduct will occur if admis­sion is not ordered.</blockquote>
                <p id="b174-6" pgmap="174">
                   When the burden of proof in the trial court is by clear and convincing evidence, our standard of review is whether the trial court’s finding is clearly erroneous. See Freeman v. Free­man, 20 Ark. App. 12, 722 S.W.2d 877 (1987). We give due def­erence to the superior position of the probate judge to evaluate the evidence. See Warren v. Tuminello, 49 Ark. App. 126, 898 S.W.2d 60 (1995). In the case at bar there is certainly ample evi­dence to support the trial court’s finding from the bench that Dr. Campbell suffered from a mental illness and needed some treat­ment. We are convinced, however, that the court’s determination that the State proved by clear and convincing evidence that Dr. Campbell posed a clear and present danger to herself or others is clearly erroneous. While two assaults were alleged in the orig­inal petition, we note that neither Lyda Campbell nor Margaret Raney gave any testimony relating to any assault. The only wit­ness at the forty-five day commitment hearing, Dr. Adkisson, testified unequivocally that Dr. Campbell did not pose a danger to herself or anyone else. We do not doubt that the probate judge was attempting to help the appellant nor do we doubt that the appellant needed help. Even so, an order of involuntary com­mitment may not issue unless the statutory requirements are met.</p>
                <p id="b174-7" pgmap="174">
                   The order of the probate court is reversed and dis­missed and the record of appellant’s involuntary commitment is to be removed from her record at the Arkansas State Hospital. See Campbell v. State, 311 Ark. 641, 846 S.W.2d 639 (1993).</p>
                <p id="b174-8" pgmap="174">Reversed and dismissed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="169" ORDERLABEL="147" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00085_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00085_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_169.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="170" ORDERLABEL="148" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00085_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00085_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_170.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="171" ORDERLABEL="149" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00086_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00086_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_171.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="172" ORDERLABEL="150" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00086_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00086_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_172.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="173" ORDERLABEL="151" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00087_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00087_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_173.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="174" ORDERLABEL="152" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00087_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00087_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_174.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b169-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_169.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b169-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_169.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b169-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_169.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b170-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_171.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b170-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b170-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ARF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_169.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b172-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_172.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b172-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_172.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b174-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_174.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b174-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_174.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b174-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_174.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b174-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_174.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b172-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_172.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b172-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_172.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b171-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_171.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b171-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_171.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AnV" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_169.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b170-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A6_" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_170.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00085_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_174.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b173-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_173.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00087_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b171-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0020"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_171.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_172.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00086_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
