<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000629_0022" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="J B Drilling Co. v. Lawrence">J B DRILLING CO. and Silvey Companies v. Arthur (Larry) LAWRENCE</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 93-335</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">45 Ark. App. 157</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">873 S.W.2d 817</citation>
          <decisiondate>1994-03-30</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T22:17:02Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T14:12:12Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-14T13:31:21Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-14T13:31:57Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00091_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ee83c0cbfc9cf5d2ac8ad18073045ace" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="11646">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00091_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00091_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8d8135b7044e2a72433023bdb339ee1b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57200">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00091_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00092_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5f4037f5fad4b3c6e2a064d82078999a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="56656">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00092_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00092_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="37bc91a15c32cd9f99cf3b56e9e177f0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="53762">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00092_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00093_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b22f329af7723dbc189254cbf7203b2d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34140">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00093_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00093_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a488e0ea0b6c38d8b24b4c221f99ed61" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34206">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00093_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00091_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="fec9986f10e24e7026bf82f714a075f9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1474374">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00091_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00091_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0fcd19d6dd22c78e2e1415cfd0cdbfc0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2669089">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00091_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00092_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="89ff9d5871a50b57f403b64485141a79" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2626515">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00092_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00092_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="1b86b0cd5c93202de460233b5a7390a4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2654919">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00092_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00093_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="61168a53678444c1b078d7c431f49f43" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2079685">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00093_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00093_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7c2a7348c6ebe23bd5d75559c3d7de9b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2377197">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000629_00093_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00091_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="fe3733bac391f35fb0a9610bec7d0dfc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="15764">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00091_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00091_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="55b19d7a73b33f55e9f8f3abbbdc46d0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="92199">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00091_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00092_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="2be6fb82332b2499b3fbfaac9ccb343c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="85041">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00092_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00092_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4cc7918a4a68c094a1b62c75cdad7d9b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="83471">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00092_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00093_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="9768e9b4740315d15e9fb39673b7bffc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="49624">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00093_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00093_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="14a56f6ddef675a17e4f1148aae5689c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="62959">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000629_redacted_ALTO_00093_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0022" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="160-B" firstpage="157">
              <court pgmap="181" id="ATL">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="181" id="b181-5">CA 93-335</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="181" id="AzI">873 S.W.2d 817</citation>
              <parties pgmap="181" id="b181-3">J B DRILLING CO. and Silvey Companies v. Arthur (Larry) LAWRENCE</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="181" id="b181-8">Opinion delivered March 30, 1994</decisiondate>
              <otherdate pgmap="181" id="A1I">[Supplemental Opinion on Denial of Rehearing May 11, 1994.]</otherdate>
              <judges pgmap="185" id="b185-7">Robbins and Rogers, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="181" id="b181-14">Daily, West, Core, Coffman &amp; Canfield, by: Eldon F. Coff-­man and Douglas M. Carson, for appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="182" id="b182-5">Bethell, Callaway, Robertson, Beasley &amp; Cowan, by: John R. Beasley, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="186" id="AAV">Eldon Coffman, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="186" id="ACfO">John Beasley, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="182" id="b182-6">John Mauzy Pittman, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="182" id="Azz">Appellants, J B Drilling Com­pany and Silvey Companies, appeal from a decision of the Work­ers’ Compensation Commission which found that appellee was entitled to compensation for an additional 2% permanent phys­ical impairment and for a 15% loss in wage-earning capacity after suffering a recurrence of a prior compensable injury. Appel­lants contend that the Commission misapplied Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-522 (1987) in making the 15% wage-loss disability award. We affirm.</p>
                <p pgmap="182" id="b182-7">Appellee sustained a compensable injury to his back on Sep­tember 1, 1987, while working for appellant J B Drilling. He subsequently underwent surgery and was assigned an anatomi­cal impairment rating of 15% to the body as a whole by his treat­ing physician. Appellants paid appellee permanent partial dis­ability benefits based on that rating. Appellee neither sought nor received benefits in excess of his percentage of permanent phys­ical impairment at that time, as he returned to work for J B Drilling in January 1988 at essentially the same wages he was receiving before the injury. In August 1989, appellee voluntar­ily terminated his employment. In December 1989, appellee suf­fered an exacerbation of the problems associated with his 1987 compensable injury, and a second back surgery was required as a result. Appellee then filed a claim for additional benefits for increased physical impairment and benefits for his loss in earn­ing capacity. Appellee testified that after the second surgery he was more limited than before in how long he could sit or stand, that he could not do any of the jobs he did before, and was no longer able to lift the weights or drive the mileage that had been required by his job with appellant J B Drilling. Medical evidence from appellee’s treating physician, Dr. Paul Raby, indicated that appellee’s physical condition had worsened after the 1989 inci­dent and resulting second surgery. Dr. Raby attributed a loss in appellee’s range of motion to the latter incident and placed restric­tions on appellee’s bending, stooping, and lifting. Dr. Raby opined that appellee now suffers an anatomical impairment of 17% to the body as a whole, 15% attributable to the September 1987 initial injury and 2% attributable to the December 1989 episode.</p>
                <p pgmap="183" id="b183-4">The Commission found that appellee had suffered a recur­rence of his original compensable injury, and that appellants remained liable therefor. The Commission found, in accordance with Dr. Raby’s opinion, that appellee had suffered an additional 2% physical impairment as a result of the recurrence. After discussing appellee’s age, education, and limited work experi­ence, together'With his present limited physical abilities, the Commission also found that appellee had suffered an additional 15% wage-loss disability. The Commission found that the dimin­ished physical abilities that adversely affected appellee’s wage-­earning capacity had occurred after he had voluntarily left his employment with J B Drilling, and thus concluded that appel­lants were liable to appellee for an additional permanent partial disability of 17% to the body as a whole (i.e., the 2% additional physical impairment and the 15% wage-loss disability).</p>
                <p pgmap="183" id="b183-5">On appeal, appellants contend that the Commission erred as a matter of law in making the award of benefits for appellee’s loss in earning capacity. Appellants argue that any award for wage-loss disability must be based solely on the 2% anatomical impairment rating associated with the 1989 recurrence. They con­tend that because appellee returned to work after his initial injury and because he voluntarily terminated that employment, he is absolutely barred from ever having the original 15% anatomical impairment considered in determining the existence or extent of any wage-loss disability. We cannot agree.</p>
                <p pgmap="183" id="b183-6">Appellants rely on Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-522(b) and (c)(2). Section 11-9-522(b) (1987) states:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="183(110) 184(24)" id="b183-7">In considering claims for permanent partial disability ben­efits in excess of the employee’s percentage of permanent physical impairment, the commission may take into account, in addition to the percentage of permanent physical impair­ment, such factors as the employee’s age, education, work experience, and other matters reasonably expected to affect his future earning capacity. However, so long as an employee, subsequent to his injury, has returned to work, has obtained other employment, or has a bona fide and reasonably obtainable offer to be employed at wages equal to or greater than his average weekly wage at the time of the accident, he shall not be entitled to permanent partial disability benefits in excess of the percentage of perma­nent physical impairment established by a preponderance of the medical testimony and evidence. [Emphasis added.]</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="184" id="b184-6">Section ll-9-522(c)(2) (1987) states in pertinent part:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="184" id="b184-7">Included in the stated intent of this section is to enable an employer to reduce or diminish payments of benefits for . .'. disability in excess of permanent physical impairment, which, in fact, no longer exists, or exists because of dis­charge for misconduct in connection with the work, or because the employee left his work voluntarily and with­out good cause connected with the work. [Emphasis added.]</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="184" id="b184-8">
                   Appellants essentially argue that, under § 11-9-522(b), a claimant who has once returned to work at equal or greater wages is permanently barred from receiving benefits for a loss in earning capacity associated with the injury that gave rise to the initial claim, regardless of whether that renewed employment should cease. However, this is precisely the same interpretation of the statute that we found erroneous in Belcher v. Holiday Inn, 43 Ark. App. 157, 868 S.W.2d 87 (1993). There, we noted that § 11-9-522(b) prohibits a claimant from receiving wage-loss only “so long as” he has returned to work, obtained other employ­ment, or has a bona fide and reasonable offer of employment. We also noted that the legislature’s intent that the bar against wage-loss benefits be other than permanent was implied in the provision for reconsideration of disability rating based on changed circumstances found in § 11-9-522(d).</p>
                <p pgmap="184" id="b184-9">Appellants’ argument under § 11-9-522(c)(2) is similar to the argument made under subsection (b). Appellants contend that subsection (c)(2) serves to bar permanently a claimant from receiving wage-loss disability benefits if subsequent to a com-­pensable injury the claimant voluntarily terminates his employ-1 ment without good cause connected with the work. We think appellants’ interpretation of this subsection is erroneous as well.</p>
                <p pgmap="184(39) 185(163)" id="b184-10">
                   Section 11-9-522(c)(2) states that benefits for wage-­loss disability are barred thereunder only when such disability “exists . . . because” the claimant left his work voluntarily and without good cause. In other words, a claimant will be barred from receiving benefits for wage-loss disability under subsec­tion (c)(2) if, but for his voluntary termination of his employ­ment, he would still be employed and thus barred from receiv­ing such benefits because of the provisions of subsection (b). Significantly, appellee neither sought nor received benefits for wage-loss disability for the period between his voluntary termi­nation of employment and the recurrence of his injury. Rather, benefits for wage-loss disability were sought and awarded only for the period after he suffered the recurrence, an intervening event that the Commission found increased appellee’s physical impairment and adversely affected his capacity to earn wages. The Commission found that, after the recurrence and resulting sec­ond surgery, appellee was incapable of performing the duties of his former employment with appellant J B Drilling; therefore, he would not still be employed in that capacity even had he not voluntarily quit, and is consequently riot barred from receiving wage-loss disability benefits by the provisions of subsection (c)(2).</p>
                <p pgmap="185" id="b185-5">
                   We cannot conclude that the Commission’s 15% wage-­loss disability award does not comport with Ark. Code Ann. §11-­9-522, and its decision is affirmed.</p>
                <p pgmap="185" id="b185-6">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
              <opinion type="rehearing">
                <p pgmap="185" id="b185-8">SUPPLEMENTAL OPINION ON DENIAL OF REHEARING MAY 11, 1994</p>
                <author pgmap="186" id="AxDu">John Mauzy Pittman, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="186" id="b186-8">
                   We recently affirmed an award of benefits to the appellee in this case. See J B Drilling Co. v. Lawrence, 45 Ark. App. 157, 873 S.W.2d 817 (1994). The appellants have filed a petition for rehearing in which they essen­tially attempt to reargue the case. This, of course, is an inap­propriate subject for a petition for rehearing. Ark. R. Sup. Ct. 2-­3(g); Nard v. State, 304 Ark. 163-A, 801 S.W.2d 634 (1991) (supp. op. on reh’g).</p>
                <p pgmap="186" id="b186-9">
                   However, we feel compelled to respond to that part of appellants’ petition in which they argue that “Appellee had the burden of proving . . . that no other job, at equal or higher pay, was available with Appellant [J B Drilling Services].” This is an incorrect statement of the law. Once it was shown that appellee had suffered a recurrence of his compensable injury and as a result could no longer perform the duties of his former job with appellant J B Drilling, which the Commission found to be the case, it was appellants’ burden to prove appellee’s receipt of a bona fide offer to be employed at wages equal to or greater than his average weekly wage at the time of the accident. See Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-522(c)(1) (1987); Cook v. Alcoa, 35 Ark. App. 16, 811 S.W.2d 329 (1991). However, as appellants con­cede in their petition, the record is silent regarding the avail­ability and offer of any such job.</p>
                <p pgmap="186" id="b186-10">Petition for rehearing denied.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="181" ORDERLABEL="157" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00091_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00091_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_181.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="182" ORDERLABEL="158" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00091_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00091_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_182.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="183" ORDERLABEL="159" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00092_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00092_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_183.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="184" ORDERLABEL="160" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00092_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00092_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_184.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="185" ORDERLABEL="160-A" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00093_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00093_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_185.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="186" ORDERLABEL="160-B" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00093_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00093_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_186.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AxDu" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b183-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_183.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b182-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_182.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b182-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_182.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b182-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_182.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b181-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b183-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_183.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AAV" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AzI" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Azz" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_182.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_182.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ATL" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ACfO" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b183-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_183.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b181-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b183-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_183.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b181-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b181-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A1I" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_181.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00091_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0022"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
