<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000682_0043" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Quinn v. Webb Wheel Products">Frank QUINN (Deceased) v. WEBB WHEEL PRODUCTS</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 97-219</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">59 Ark. App. 272</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">957 S.W.2d 187</citation>
          <decisiondate>1997-12-17</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-21T23:20:31Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:11:05Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-25T13:10:58Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170721.post180</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-25T13:11:57Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170721.post180</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00150_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="52d3457fee46be2034d51018aedae82c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="26792">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00150_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00151_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="8ea96cd113fe7f58ccd5b026a7c140cf" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3958">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00151_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00151_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7066549498630cea84026e3eb4af6956" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="30532">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00151_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00152_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="f6dc3a09d2e7f3d1e8b16bf3bc939e72" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54710">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00152_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00152_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0e71bb89e8c0660330452415614de03e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="55072">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00152_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00153_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="94a13da4957ef522a2a89a1242222401" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="43018">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00153_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00150_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cb2f3bed0163b166bb1146fb0fd5ea0d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2088142">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00150_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00151_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="02c6aa1d74ccc2bbe881afea26b236ed" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1134100">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00151_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00151_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="b3282ee6e67d466d00cacb1c8da01d2a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2026878">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00151_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00152_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="5d03341dfd834645b631335bbb434a1e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2580800">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00152_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00152_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="f52d8c218594f9136e60c92b4f9c22fb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2594826">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00152_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00153_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="fb913d173c5149f729d3a72ca4659708" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2573916">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000682_00153_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00150_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ef38ed0cc087ed12c69a137a1aa4920f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="41650">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00150_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00151_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e5dea2e753f7dd3b09752c5d5795e734" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1779">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00151_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00151_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="efc54f2660996b8cb320edfa5ccf947d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="46318">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00151_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00152_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c2b436aa3dbf4cb7edcc95f0aeb1da66" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="87423">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00152_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00152_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="53622efe834b0832b60a906a3ac8034d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="90448">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00152_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00153_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="5bb69d73ad08d301c0c82d00aa31b576" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="69409">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000682_redacted_ALTO_00153_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0043" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="277" firstpage="272">
              <court pgmap="300" id="b300-9">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Divisions I and II</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="300" id="AsV">CA 97-219</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="300" id="Apv">957 S.W.2d 187</citation>
              <parties pgmap="300" id="b300-8">Frank QUINN (Deceased) v. WEBB WHEEL PRODUCTS</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="300" id="b300-10">Opinion delivered December 17, 1997</decisiondate>
              <otherdate pgmap="300" id="A0G">[Petition for rehearing denied January 14, 1998.]</otherdate>
              <judges pgmap="305" id="b305-8">Robbins, CJ., and Pittman, Jennings, Rogers, and Meads, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="302" id="b302-9">Tolley &amp; Brooks, P.A., by: Jay N. Tolley, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="302" id="b302-10">Michale H. Mashbum, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="302" id="b302-11">Winston Bryant, Att’y Gen., by: Leigh Anne Yeargan, Asst. Att’y Gen., amicus curiae, for the Workers’ Compensation Commission.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="302" id="b302-12">Olly Neal, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="302" id="A2Z">This is the second appeal to this court of this workers’ compensation matter. In Quinn v. Webb Wheel, 52 Ark. App. 208, 915 S.W.2d 740 (1996), we remanded for the Commission’s consideration, the appellant’s challenge to the con­stitutionality of Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-201 (Repl. 1996). On remand, the Commission held that the composition of the Com­mission does not deny claimants due process of law. In the present appeal, appellant contends that Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-201, must be found unconstitutional because the manner in which the Workers’ Compensation Commission members are chosen denies litigants due process of law. For reasons discussed herein, we hold that Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-201 is constitutional.</p>
                <p pgmap="302(34) 303(118)" id="b302-13">Appellant argues that the Commission should be abolished because at least two members are not impartial and independent, but instead are aligned and identified with respective interests. The Arkansas Workers’ Compensation Commission is comprised of three members who are appointed by the Governor for terms of six years, and are required to devote their entire time to the duties of the Commission. Ark. Code Ann. § ll-9-201(a) (Repl. 1996). One member must have been an attorney who has represented employers in workers’ compensation matters for at least five years or an individual who has been an employer; one member must have represented employees for at least five years in workers’ com­pensation matters; and the third member, the chairman of the Commission, must have been engaged in the active practice of law in the State of Arkansas for five years preceding his appointment. See Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-201 (a)(1)(2)(3) (Repl. 1996).</p>
                <p pgmap="303" id="b303-5">Appellant argues that the statute creating the Workers’ Com­pensation Commission is unconstitutional because the affiliation of the commissioners to certain interests is violative of the Due Process Clauses of both the Arkansas and United States Constitu­tions. This argument assumes that at least two Commission mem­bers have inherent prejudices or biases stemming from their former business relationships. The particular issue is heretofore undecided by our courts. Therefore, we must look to other courts for guidance in this matter.</p>
                <p pgmap="303" id="b303-6">
                   The United States Supreme Court has identified three factors to be considered when determining what type of due process is warranted. See Matthews v. Eldridge, 424 U.S. 319 (1976). The factors to be considered are (1) the private interest that will be affected by the official action; (2) the risk of an erro­neous deprivation of such interest through the procedures used, and probable value, if any, of additional procedural safeguards; and (3) the government’s interest, including fiscal and administrative burdens that the additional or substitute procedures would entail. Id. at 332. We have no difficulty in declaring that the private interest in workers’ compensation disability benefits is considera­ble. Nor do we hesitate in concluding that additional or substitute procedures would not be unduly burdensome. However, even though additional procedures would not be unduly burdensome, appellant has faded to show that they would provide any additional protections. We therefore focus on the second Matthews factor, i.e., the risk of an erroneous deprivation of the protected interest through the procedures used.</p>
                <p pgmap="304" id="b304-4">
                   We begin with the premise that an adjudicator is pre­sumed to be unbiased, and to overcome that presumption, a liti­gant must make a showing of a conflict of interest or some other specific reason for disqualification. See Withrow v. Larkin, 421 U.S. 35, 37 (1975); Gibson v. Berryhill, 411 U.S. 564 (1973); Ward v. Village of Monroeville, 409 U.S. 57, 60 (1972). In general, the test is whether the adjudicator’s situation is one that might lead him not to hold the balance [between the parties] clear and true. Turney v. Ohio, 273 U.S. 510 (1927).</p>
                <p pgmap="304" id="b304-5">In Williams v. Hofley Mfg. Co., 424 N.W.2d 278 (Mich. 1988), the Supreme Court of Michigan held that the fact that members of the Workers’ Compensation Appeal Board are desig­nated as representatives of employer interests, of employee inter­ests, or of the general public, did not create pecuniary interest and, the employer was not denied due process by a hearing before a two-member interest-designed panel. The court reasoned that although members were drawn from the ranks of attorneys repre­senting divergent interests, members were forbidden by statute from engaging in any other business or professional activity and were required to devote their entire time to performing the duties of their office. The court reasoned further, that the statutory pro­visions for appointment, service, and removal of members of the Workers’ Compensation Appeal Board did not require that mem­bers continue to advocate interests of a designated group, much less bind members to decide cases on the basis of the views of interest groups from which they were selected, and therefore, the employer was not denied procedural due process.</p>
                <p pgmap="304(107) 305(121)" id="b304-6">
                   The findings made by the Commission reveal noth­ing that would support or indicate bias in the Commission’s deci­sions. Similarly, there is nothing inherent in the composition of the Arkansas Workers’ Compensation Commission that would make the manner in which its members are selected unconstitu­tional. The fact that the members of the Commission are selected based upon their status as former employers or employer repre­sentatives or as former employees or employee representatives does not in any way create the alleged inherent bias argued by appel­lant. The controversy seems to stem from members of the Com­mission being classed as representatives. Representative has been defined as “standing or acting for another especially through dele­gated authority.” Webster’s Ninth New Collegiate Dictionary, 1000 (9th ed. 1990). Representative is also defined as “a typical exam­ple of a group, class, or quality.” Id. We believe that the latter definition of “representative” more adequately expresses the true nature of the “representative” contemplated by the statute. Fur­ther, we believe that the designation of commissioners as employee or employer representative merely refers to the particu­larized knowledge that each commissioner possesses with respect to the divergent interests present in workers’ compensation claims. Nowhere is this more clear than in the statutory requirement that commissioners have five years’ experience in their respective fields to qualify for appointment to the Commission.</p>
                <p pgmap="305" id="b305-5">Members of the Commission are full-time commissioners. As such, they are required to devote their entire time to the duties of the Commission, and are not required to advocate the interests of a special group. Further, there is no pecuniary gain to. the commissioners based upon the manner in which they vote, because their salary is determined by our state legislature and not private-interest groups. See Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-201 (3)(b) (Repl. 1996).</p>
                <p pgmap="305" id="b305-6">
                   It is well settled that an act by the legislature is enti­tled to a presumption of constitutionality. Golden v. Westark Com­munity College, 58 Ark. App. 209, 948 S.W.2d 108 (1997). The party challenging a statute has the burden of proving it unconstitu­tional. See Lambert v. Baldor Elec., 44 Ark. App. 117, 868 S.W.2d 513 (1993). In the present case, appellant has not shown that the manner in which members of the Commission are appointed vio­lates his due process rights.</p>
                <p pgmap="305" id="b305-7">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="300" ORDERLABEL="272" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00150_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00150_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_300.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="301" ORDERLABEL="273" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00151_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00151_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00151_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_301.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="302" ORDERLABEL="274" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00151_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00151_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_302.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="303" ORDERLABEL="275" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00152_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00152_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00152_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_303.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="304" ORDERLABEL="276" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00152_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00152_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00152_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_304.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="305" ORDERLABEL="277" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00153_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00153_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_305.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b302-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b302-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_303.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b302-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b302-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b300-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b300-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b303-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_303.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b303-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_303.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b305-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_305.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b305-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_305.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Apv" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b304-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_304.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b305-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_305.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b304-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_304.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_305.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AsV" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b305-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_305.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00153_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A0G" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b304-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_304.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00152_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b300-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_300.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b302-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A2Z" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0043"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_302.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00151_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
