<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000712_0037" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="McGrath v. Carson">Mark McGRATH v. Randall L. CARSON, M.D.</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 02-168</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">79 Ark. App. 269</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">86 S.W.3d 415</citation>
          <decisiondate>2002-10-09</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T02:12:41Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-15T21:41:47Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-19T12:54:20Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-19T12:57:26Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00148_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="2a1e734fb4233c1506a94e22605d61f1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="7226">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00148_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00148_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b93553d54a0a1b01eb62d065bc6c6ba7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="24198">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00148_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00149_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="025e42c521bee3800bb007ea16ca55b3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="52274">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00149_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00149_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e43093cd26b65d7639b40b5033def278" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="47474">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00149_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00150_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4a0851724c4c0212e3cd2b50132d8f34" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="46380">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00150_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00148_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="813f49ade00e6834e6a4dd0d467f1373" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1457072">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00148_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00148_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="2d90d7b20f03b3ae77aa0af7e290fbf8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1862746">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00148_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00149_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cdbba29a72b19b9d4f50b3259a7f78cc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2598078">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00149_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00149_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="1b5447ae1f7ef8e78ec15d022690b3a3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2516919">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00149_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00150_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="9722b7754e1d7a403e67122122aeb20c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2476466">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000712_00150_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00148_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7a54e0101855f62093930f7285e4f545" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="8259">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000712_redacted_ALTO_00148_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00148_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6001e7c2d5386a3a36fef2c58b369d01" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="36743">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000712_redacted_ALTO_00148_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00149_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c333860ef0b66d385f4813da73054155" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="88728">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000712_redacted_ALTO_00149_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00149_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="b629c6643db5f30fb09a1cb770310b8b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="93961">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000712_redacted_ALTO_00149_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00150_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4dac6695b7651ad14c16cbd3c64aed2d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="82023">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000712_redacted_ALTO_00150_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0037" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="269" lastpage="273">
              <court pgmap="295" id="b295-5">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division III</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="295" id="b295-4">CA 02-168</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="295" id="ADp">86 S.W.3d 415</citation>
              <parties pgmap="295" id="b295-3">Mark McGRATH v. Randall L. CARSON, M.D.</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="295" id="b295-6">Opinion delivered October 9, 2002</decisiondate>
              <judges pgmap="299" id="b299-8">Bird, J., agrees.</judges>
              <judges pgmap="299" id="b299-9">Robbins, J., concurs.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="296" id="b296-9">J. Randolph Shock; and Jerry D. Pruitt, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="296" id="b296-10">Warner, Smith &amp; Harris, PLC, by: G. Alan Wooten and Mat­thew C. Carter, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="296" id="b296-11">John Mauzy Pittman, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="296(116) 297(56)" id="A9Q">The decedent in this med­ical malpractice case was an obese woman who had a his­tory of suspected blood clots in her lower legs and who had recently had gall bladder surgery. She had been maintained on birth-control medication, which increases the risk of clotting, throughout these incidents. She presented at appellee’s office complaining of shortness of breath, tachycardia, elevated blood pressure, and chest pains. The appellee stated that he considered coronary, pulmonary, esophageal, and arterial problems in attempting to diagnose her condition. He ultimately performed several tests, including a chest x-ray, and prescribed Tenormin, a drug used in the treatment of hypertension. Three days later the patient returned in much-worsened condition, was admitted to the hospital by appellee, and died there shortly thereafter of a pul­monary embolism. Appellant, the decedent’s husband, brought a wrongful death action against several entities and physicians, including appellee, alleging that they were guilty of negligent mal­practice resulting in the decedent’s death. The jury found in favor of the defendants, and this appeal followed.</p>
                <p pgmap="297" id="b297-5">For reversal, appellant contends that the trial court erred in failing to direct a verdict in his favor; in failing to grant judgment for him notwithstanding the verdict; and in failing to grant him a new trial on grounds that the verdict was contrary to the evidence. We affirm.</p>
                <p pgmap="297" id="b297-6">
                   The standard of review is essentially the same for all of appellant’s arguments. McWilliams v. Schmidt, 76 Ark. App. 173, 61 S.W.3d 898 (2001); Home Mutual Fire Insurance Co. v. Jones, 63 Ark. App. 221, 977 S.W.2d 12 (1998). Review of the denial of a motion for directed verdict is directed toward deter­mining whether the jury’s verdict is supported by substantial evi­dence; in reviewing the denial of a motion for judgment notwithstanding the verdict, the question is whether there is no substantial evidence to support the jury’s verdict and the moving party is entitled to judgment as a matter of law, Wal-Mart Stores, Inc. v. Lee, 348 Ark. 707, 74 S.W.3d 634 (2002); the denial of a motion for new trial will not be reversed on appeal if the verdict is supported by substantial evidence. McWilliams v. Schmidt, supra. Substantial evidence is evidence that is of sufficient certainty and precision to compel a conclusion one way or another, forcing or inducing the mind to pass beyond suspicion or conjecture and, on appeal, we will only consider the evidence favorable to the appel-­lee, together with all its reasonable inferences, in determining whether the evidence is substantial. Home Mutual Fire Insurance Co. v. Jones, supra.</p>
                <p pgmap="297(64) 298(35)" id="b297-7">
                   It is significant that, in the present case, appellant was plaintiff below when he moved for directed verdict and judg­ment notwithstanding the verdict. Given that appellant had the burden of proof below, a directed verdict or judgment notwith­standing the verdict would be proper only if there were no rational basis whatsoever for the jury to do other than believe the proof he presented at trial. Former Justice George Rose Smith discussed the formidable standard applicable to review of this particular question in Morton v. American Medical International, Inc., 286 Ark. 88, 90, 689 S.W.2d 535, 536-37 (1985):</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="298" id="b298-6">We are not aware of any Arkansas case in which a verdict for the party not having the burden of proof has been set aside in a negli­gence case solely because it was not supported by substantial evidence.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="298" id="b298-7">The argument now made is presented so rarely that it sel­dom finds its way into the books. We did consider it in Spink v. Mourton, 235 Ark. 919, 362 S.W.2d 665 (1962). There the plaintiff, having lost below, argued that there was no substantial evidence to support the verdict and that (as it would logically follow) a verdict should have been directed for the plaintiff. In rejecting that argument we quoted with approval this language from United States Fire Ins. Co. v. Milner Hotels, 253 F.2d 542 (8th Cir. 1958):</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="298" id="b298-8">Thus, no matter how strong the evidence of a party, who has the burden of establishing negligence and proxi­mate cause as facts, may comparatively seem to be, he is not entitled to have those facts declared to have reality as a mat­ter of law, unless there is utterly no rational basis in the situ­ation, testimonially, circumstantially, or inferentially, for a jury to believe otherwise.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="298" id="b298-9">The Supreme Court of Missouri correctly stated the com­mon law rule, which also governs in Arkansas, in Cluck v. Abe, 328 Mo. 81, 40 S.W.2d 558 (1931):</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="298" id="b298-10">The burden was not on the defendant, but was on the plaintiff to make out the case stated in his petition. In a case where the allegations of the petition are denied by the answer, and the plaintiff offers oral evidence tending to sup­port the allegations of the petition, the defendant is entitled to have the jury pass upon the credibility of such evidence even though he should offer no evidence himself. The court has no right to tell the jury that it must believe the witnesses. The jury, in the first instance, is the sole judge of the credibility of the witnesses and of the weight and value of their evidence, and may believe or disbelieve the testi­mony of any one or all of the witnesses, though such evi­dence be uncontradicted and unimpeached.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="299" id="b299-4">See Webb v. Bouton, 350 Ark. 254, 85 S.W.3d 885 (2002).</p>
                <p pgmap="299" id="b299-5">Appellant presents a very narrow issue on appeal: was the jury required to conclude, on the basis of the evidence before it, that appellee was negligent in failing to order a VQ scan that would have detected the pulmonary embolism? We note that the appellee himself stated in a deposition that he would definitely have ordered the VQ scan had he suspected a pulmonary embo­lism, but admitted at trial that he had, in fact, suspected a pulmo­nary embolism but did not order that particular test to be per­formed.</p>
                <p pgmap="299" id="b299-6">
                   Nevertheless, we think that the resolution of this con­flict in the evidence was for the jury, and that there was evidence from which the jury could have inferred that appellee was not negligent in failing to order a VQ scan. Although appellant has argued that appellee was required to do so if he simply suspected that the decedent had a pulmonary embolism, we believe the real question is whether appellee had sufficient indications to give him such a reasonable suspicion that a pulmonary embolism was present that it would have been negligent not to order the VQ scan at that time. Given the extensive evidence at trial to show that pulmo­nary embolism is an extremely difficult condition to diagnose; that appellee was not a pulmonary specialist but instead a general prac­titioner; that one of the cardinal symptoms of pulmonary embo­lism (coughing up blood) was absent when appellant presented to appellee; that decedent’s symptoms of shortness of breath and chest pain could have been caused by a wide range of diseases; and that appellee did order a chest x-ray that is ninety percent effective in detecting whether pulmonary embolism is present and which failed to detect any evidence of embolism at that time; we think that the jury could reasonably have found that appellee was not negligent in failing to order the VQ scan at the time of her initial office visit.</p>
                <p pgmap="299" id="b299-7">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="295" ORDERLABEL="269" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00148_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00148_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_295.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="296" ORDERLABEL="270" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00148_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00148_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_296.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="297" ORDERLABEL="271" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00149_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00149_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_297.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="298" ORDERLABEL="272" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00149_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00149_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_298.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="299" ORDERLABEL="273" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00150_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00150_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_299.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b298-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b298-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b299-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_299.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00150_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b298-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b298-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b297-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_297.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b297-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_297.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b297-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_297.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ADp" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b298-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_298.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A9Q" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_297.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00149_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b296-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_296.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b295-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0037"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_295.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00148_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
