<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000695_0009" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Hill v. State">Christopher HILL v. STATE of Arkansas</name>
          <docketnumber>CA CR 93-640</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">47 Ark. App. 44</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">883 S.W.2d 857</citation>
          <decisiondate>1994-10-05</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-23T01:24:43Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T15:58:32Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T13:32:01Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T13:32:56Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00033_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a2c95c977f719404d9a7ffea3890d9cc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="22856">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00033_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00034_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b1c3fe9f8cf7c8ee0ecb983cc29b734d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54822">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00034_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00034_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7b734a0643ca94f22b9a5c4ae0714f76" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57080">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00034_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00035_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="70038a4b9b2ab5aa6c101b4e8f3f6905" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="53982">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00035_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00035_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c928ef474f5008861ac77fa14b90a212" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="10470">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00035_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00033_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="44c02832eeff65c1193d60832c68a621" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1839345">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00033_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00034_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="fcdc49f562aba96f64ae06dc6b92df02" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2625297">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00034_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00034_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cf355f297a15521e36d2cadb503803f7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2643627">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00034_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00035_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0e7953015ab8d5beb8da75fbab4871a8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2603723">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00035_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00035_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a8c07940480ef38ffc32e91887344122" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1508939">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000695_00035_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00033_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f24f6ce56869266e3f1f64c5e696bdf9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="38369">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000695_redacted_ALTO_00033_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00034_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="430e1038fab63b34212720775c81c9a8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="98530">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000695_redacted_ALTO_00034_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00034_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="16df0777729e960b8c61641d068a5d2c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="106501">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000695_redacted_ALTO_00034_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00035_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="ab638fa78f2d656a56ce20c99ab799ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="101780">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000695_redacted_ALTO_00035_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00035_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="740096d91a4e18de24f584e77dab19bd" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="13625">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000695_redacted_ALTO_00035_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0009" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="48" firstpage="44">
              <court pgmap="66" id="b66-4">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="66" id="AZh">CA CR 93-640</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="66" id="AhXq">883 S.W.2d 857</citation>
              <parties pgmap="66" id="b66-3">Christopher HILL v. STATE of Arkansas</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="66" id="b66-5">Opinion delivered October 5, 1994</decisiondate>
              <judges pgmap="70" id="b70-7">Cooper and Robbins, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="66" id="b66-10">Green &amp; Henry, by: J. Bradley Green, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="66" id="b66-11">Winston Bryant, Att’y Gen., by: /. Brent Standridge, Asst. Att’y Gen., for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="66" id="b66-12">Judith Rogers, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="66" id="APx0">The trial court, sitting as the trier of fact, found the appellant, Christopher Hill, guilty of possession of a controlled substance (cocaine) with intent to deliver, and sen­tenced him to a term of twenty-five years in prison of which thir­teen years were suspended. The sole issue on appeal is appel­lant’s contention that he did not voluntarily and knowingly waive a trial by jury, and thus was denied the right to a jury trial. Because the waiver of a jury trial was not accomplished in the manner pre­scribed by law, we must reverse and remand for a new trial.</p>
                <p pgmap="67" id="b67-5">The record discloses that, at the conclusion of a pre-trial hearing held the day before trial, there was some discussion between court and counsel about postponing appellant’s jury trial. It appears that there were other cases scheduled for trial on the same date, a situation which might pose a problem since the tri­als had been set on election day and the courtroom would be needed for counting votes. During this discourse, counsel for the defense pointed out that appellant had been in jail for three months awaiting trial, and he requested “either a real fast trial” or that appellant be released on his own recognizance. The prosecution was not amenable to the request for appellant’s release, given appellant’s out-of-state contacts and the gravity of the offense, which was said to involve some seventeen rocks of cocaine. As an alternative, the prosecution suggested that the case proceed to trial the next day as planned, but without a jury. Counsel for the defense responded to the prosecutor’s suggestion by asking for a few moments to discuss the proposition with appellant. The hear­ing was then brought to a close by the court saying, “All right. Well, I don’t want to try it tomorrow frankly. Two trials in one day would be plenty for me without a third one. We’re congested but we’re not that bad.” The record reveals nothing further on the jury-versus-bench trial matter, but a bench trial was held the fol­lowing day without any apparent objection from appellant.</p>
                <p pgmap="67" id="b67-6">Article 2, section 7 of the Arkansas Constitution provides that a jury trial may be waived “in the manner prescribed by law.” The manner prescribed by law, as applicable to criminal cases, is set out in Rule 31.2 of the Arkansas Rules of Criminal Procedure. This rule provides:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="67" id="b67-7">Should a defendant desire to waive his right to trial by jury, he must do so personally either in writing or in open court. A verbatim record of any proceedings at which a defendant waives his right to a trial by jury shall be made and preserved.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="67(77) 68(115)" id="b67-8">
                   When construing the constitutional provision together with Rule 31.2. the supreme court held in Calnan v. State, 310 Ark. 744, 841 S.W.2d 593 (1992)', that ”[t]he law is clear that the only way a defendant may waive the jury trial right is by per­sonally making an express declaration in writing or in open court and that the open court proceedings where the defendant waives his or her right must be preserved.” In Calnan, the court also determined that this right could not be forfeited by a defendant’s inaction, and ruled that the burden is on the trial court to assure that any waiver of the right to a trial by jury is accomplished in accordance with the requirements of the law. The court thus con­cluded that the contemporaneous objection rule did not apply. Since the record in that case contained no waiver of the right to a jury trial, the supreme court found merit in the appellant’s argu­ment that her right to a jury trial had been violated, and it reversed and remanded for a new trial. See also Winkle v. State, 310 Ark. 713, 841 S.W.2d 589 (1992).</p>
                <p pgmap="68" id="b68-6">
                   More recently, the supreme court decided the cases of Bolt v. State, 314 Ark. 387, 862 S.W.2d 841 (1993), and Johnson v. State, 314 Ark. 471, 863 S.W.2d 305 (1993), 314 Ark. 478, 868 S.W.2d 43 (1993) (supplemental opinion denying rehearing). In Bolt v. State, the appellant had signed a form acknowledging his right to a jury trial, and later his counsel, in open court and in the appellant’s presence, waived a jury trial and asked the trial court to hear the case. Similarly, in Johnson v. State, the attorney had stated in open court and in the appellant’s presence that the right to a jury trial was being waived in favor of a bench trial. The sit­uation in Johnson differed from that in Bolt only in that the appel­lant in Johnson had not been presented with a form which specif­ically apprised the accused of the right to a jury trial. In both cases the appellants urged, relying on the decisions in Calnan v. State, supra, and Winkle v. State, supra, that their waivers did not meet the requirements of the rule because they were made by their attor­neys, and not “personally” by them. The supreme court disagreed, holding that an attorney’s waiver made on the record in the pres­ence of the defendant satisfied the requirements of the law. The court in Johnson specifically stated that under those circumstances a defendant may not stand idly by and later cry foul.</p>
                <p pgmap="68(99) 69(40)" id="b68-7">In the present case, after the appellant had filed his brief with this court, the State filed a motion to settle the record. In this motion, the State asserted that it had learned that, despite the record’s silence, there had been a discussion, presumably in appellant’s presence, in which appellant’s counsel had informed the trial court that appellant agreed to waive the right to a jury trial. The State specifically made reference to the cases of Bolt v. State supra, and Johnson v. State, supra, which were then pending in the supreme court. In further support of the motion, the State noted that the trial court’s docket entry from the pre­trial hearing contained the notation that a jury trial had been waived. We granted the motion and directed the trial court to conduct a hearing on the matter.</p>
                <p pgmap="69" id="b69-6">On remand, and after the hearing, the trial court entered an order in which it made the following findings of fact. The court found that, at the conclusion of the pre-trial hearing, appellant and his counsel retired to the library to discuss proceeding with a non-jury trial. The court found that counsel advised appellant of the differences between a jury and non-jury trial, and dis­cussed what possibilities could occur and what the likely out­come would be. The court also found that appellant wanted his case tried quickly, that he understood the differences between a jury and non-jury trial, and that he advised his attorney that he wished to proceed with trial the next day. The trial court then found that “[o]ff the record, after Mr. Smith [defense counsel] had the conversation with the defendant, Mr. Smith went into the Court’s chambers and advised the Court and the state’s attorney that the defendant agreed, after consultation with Mr. Smith, to waive his right to a jury trial.”</p>
                <p pgmap="69(161) 70(14)" id="b69-7">
                   Confining our review to the record of the pre-trial hearing and of trial, we are faced with a situation like that which was denounced in both the cases of Calnan v. State, supra, and Winkle v. State, supra, in that a bench trial was held without the record reflecting an express waiver of the right to a jury trial. In those cases and their progeny, the supreme court has spoken, commanding that the right to a jury trial must be waived in writ­ing or on the record in open court, either by the appellant him­self or by his attorney in the defendant’s presence. Since the record here is conspicuously silent, we are compelled to find merit in the appellant’s argument that he was denied the right to a jury trial. Even considering the record as reconstructed on remand,<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> the result would be the same since the trial court found that the waiver was communicated by defense counsel in cham­bers without appellant being present and without a record being made of the colloquy.</p>
                <p pgmap="70" id="b70-6">Reversed and Remanded.</p>
                <footnote label="1">
                  <p pgmap="69" id="b69-8">1 Given the requirement found in Rule 31.2 that a verbatim record be made, we question whether the record can be settled in this instance to reflect that which was done, but yet not recorded. We do not question, however, the State’s good faith in ask­ing for the record to be settled to include that which may have been simply omitted from the record brought up on appeal.</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="66" ORDERLABEL="44" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00033_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00033_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_66.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="67" ORDERLABEL="45" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00034_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00034_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_67.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="68" ORDERLABEL="46" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00034_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00034_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00034_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_68.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="69" ORDERLABEL="47" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00035_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00035_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_69.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="70" ORDERLABEL="48" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00035_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00035_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00035_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_70.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="APx0" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b70-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_70.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b70-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_70.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b68-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_68.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b68-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_68.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_69.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AZh" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AhXq" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b66-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_66.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00033_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b67-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_67.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b67-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_67.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b67-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_67.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b69-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_69.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b69-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_69.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_70.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b69-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_69.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00035_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b67-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0009"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_67.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_68.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00034_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
