<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000726_0011" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Barnard v. B &amp; M Construction">Bruce BARNARD v. B &amp; M CONSTRUCTION</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 95-247</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">52 Ark. App. 61</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">915 S.W.2d 296</citation>
          <decisiondate>1996-02-14</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T23:09:59Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-15T21:53:18Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T01:55:37Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T01:58:11Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00042_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="551c1200decd323d904bd32c020c5309" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="29504">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00042_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00042_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ac6ea8a8a4f1dc841a6eb2cc5bb05dc8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="23112">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00042_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00043_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="866050be1e9f398481ac6629ae37d07c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="55474">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00043_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00043_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a872dec56b4093f0209c1f399ce6443c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="48462">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00043_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00044_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="b2fe2c370ec78ecad1611d40b2505086" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="51166">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00044_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00044_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="adf7ab6dc361766e11799fced07d0f6d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="13836">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00044_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00042_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="c42cd4403a58882b4cdd34a634d5f765" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2154468">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00042_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00042_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="e19f7d0674c7b7c8039d128d94127319" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1620395">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00042_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00043_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="dd08cd07dd41a2effba9d4bf8194886d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2617742">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00043_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00043_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d23157a9e512ab5a97b68435da4e0a1b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2466711">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00043_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00044_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="66eb02cbe7aea6aab431155967ba59ae" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2635032">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00044_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00044_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="bcc55e6d1ac22609e714f4d8e55163c0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1537681">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000726_00044_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00042_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7b9f629c666801e0f864026360f84939" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="47270">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00042_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00042_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="736593efb9ccf705fc22226105fc9aaa" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="32908">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00042_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00043_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="7bbec82f9104ada046e5c0ce8ea96f59" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="93014">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00043_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00043_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f441786fc03045a9c700673fa720468b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86813">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00043_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00044_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f8751bbb3d26aa2d1f0c6973904f16f5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="88690">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00044_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00044_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="76e5feb2d06047ab4b6da83455e173de" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="18377">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000726_redacted_ALTO_00044_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0011" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="66" firstpage="61">
              <court id="b83-8" pgmap="83">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber id="Amo" pgmap="83">CA 95-247</docketnumber>
              <citation id="AIC" pgmap="83">915 S.W.2d 296</citation>
              <parties id="b83-7" pgmap="83">Bruce BARNARD v. B &amp; M CONSTRUCTION</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b83-9" pgmap="83">Opinion delivered February 14, 1996</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b88-7" pgmap="88">Cooper and Griffen, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b84-11" pgmap="84">Lane, Muse, Arman &amp; Pullen, by: R. Keith Arman, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b84-12" pgmap="84">Anderson &amp; Kilpatrick, by: Michael P. Vanderford, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b84-13" pgmap="84">John F. Stroud, Jr., Judge.</author>
                <p id="AqF" pgmap="84(105) 85(17)">Bruce Barnard was employed as a construction worker by B &amp; M Construction Company on February 10, 1992, when he fell from a steel beam onto a concrete floor, striking his head. He suffered a closed head injury and had headaches and double vision. B &amp; M Con­struction accepted the claim as compensable and paid temporary total disability and medical benefits. At a hearing before the administrative law judge, Mr. Barnard contended that he was entitled to a physical impairment rating due to loss of vision. The law judge denied and dismissed the claim. After conducting a de novo review, the Workers’ Compensation Commission affirmed and adopted the decision of the administrative law judge. We affirm the denial of the claim.</p>
                <p id="b85-5" pgmap="85">
                   The claimant raises one point on appeal, stating that he has shown by substantial evidence that he has sustained per­manent disability as a result of his admittedly compensable injury. This is not the standard by which we review cases when the Commission has denied a claim. Where, as here, the Com­mission denies a claim because the claimant has failed to show entitlement by a preponderance of the evidence, the substantial evidence standard of review requires that we affirm if the Com­mission’s opinion displays a substantial basis for the denial of relief. Brantley v. Tyson Foods, Inc., 48 Ark. App. 27, 887 S.W.2d 543 (1994). Substantial evidence means such relevant evidence as a reasonable mind might accept as adequate to sup­port a conclusion. Wright v. ABC Air, Inc., 44 Ark. App. 5, 864 S.W.2d 871 (1993). On appeal, we are required to view the evi­dence in the light most favorable to the findings and give the testimony its strongest probative force in favor of the Commis­sion’s action. Tyson Foods, Inc. v. Disheroon, 26 Ark. App. 145, 761 S.W.2d 617 (1988).</p>
                <p id="b85-6" pgmap="85">The evidence, which includes testimony by the claimant as well as medical testimony and records, shows that the claimant reported headaches and vision problems after the accident. The claimant stated that he continued to have double vision when viewing objects up to four and one-half feet away. Dr. Michael Brodsky followed the claimant at Arkansas Children’s Hospital Eye Clinic. Dr. Brodsky diagnosed the claimant’s vision prob­lem as convergence insufficiency and prescribed reading glasses with prisms incorporated into them in order to see objects close­up and use his eyes together to avoid double vision.</p>
                <p id="b85-7" pgmap="85(101) 86(33)">In support of his claim for permanent disability, the claim­ant refers to his need to wear two pairs of glasses to see prop­erly. He points to the testimony of ophthalmologist Dr. Thomas R. Wallace that a change of glasses would be required for switching from close to distant work, such as when leaving close­up work at a bench to walk across a room. The claimant con­cludes that he can no longer do construction work because he cannot walk while wearing the prism glasses which he must wear for working with a screwdriver or hammer and nails. The claimant states, however, that he has a riding lawnmower, a push mower, and a leaf mower; that he is able to do lawn work; and that he is able to drive a car.</p>
                <p id="b86-6" pgmap="86">The medical evidence includes conflicting reports concern­ing the claimant’s fields of vision. Dr. Wallace, in determining the claimant’s impairment rating, referred to testing the visual fields. His report of March 15, 1994, states:</p>
                <blockquote id="b86-7" pgmap="86">I have calculated Mr. Barnard’s disability based on my interpretation of Guide to the Evaluation of Permanent Impairment, Third Edition Revised. . . .</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b86-8" pgmap="86">Right eye appears to be his worse [sic]. He has 20/20 vision in that eye for no central vision loss. His visual field loss is approximately 47%. This is an inferior hemia-­nopia and according to the above mentioned book this entitles him to an addition 10% of loss, so his visual field loss in the right eye is 47% plus 10% or 57%. Combining this with the 57% loss of the right eye using the combined value chart shows a 100% loss in the right eye.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b86-9" pgmap="86">The left eye has no loss of central vision. He has lost 10% visual field with an extra 5% because he has lost an infer­ior quadrant yielding 15% loss of visual field. Combining these on the combined value chart yields 16%.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b86-10" pgmap="86">When you combine the impairment in the worse eye (right) 100% and the better eye (left) 16% and ... an impairment of the visual system of 38%. . . this shows an impairment of the whole person of 36%.</blockquote>
                <p id="b86-11" pgmap="86">The claimant’s visual fields were also tested by Dr. George Schroeder, an ophthalmologist, and Dr. John Stuckey, an optometrist. In a letter of June 13, 1994, optometrist Dr. Thomas H. Gulley compares their test results to those which Dr. Wallace obtained. Dr. Gulley states in his letter:</p>
                <blockquote id="b86-12" pgmap="86">These fields were done on the same type of instrument and the same threshold levels as at Dr. Tom Wallace’s office. As you can see, the results are somewhat different and on both tests, it states there is low patient reliability.</blockquote>
                <p id="b86-13" pgmap="86(21) 87(2)">In a letter dated July 21, 1994, Dr. Gulley evaluates the claimant’s corrected vision and refers to the subjective nature of the testing:</p>
                <blockquote id="b87-5" pgmap="87">This is in response to [respondents’] questions. Bruce Bar­nard has corrected vision of 20/20 in both eyes. In other words, while wearing his glasses his vision is normal.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b87-6" pgmap="87">The disability rating given by Dr. Tom Wallace is based on the threshold test which is used to determine any defi­cit in Mr. Barnard’s field of vision. Dr. Wallace did the test on two occasions and the results were different in each instance. I sent Mr. Barnard to Drs. Stuckey and Schroeder on June 9, 1994, to have that test performed. The results of the test performed by Dr. Stuckey and Schroeder are different than those done by Dr. Wallace. And it states on the test form that there is low patient reliability on all the tests. The validity of these tests is based on the answers given by Mr. Barnard. Because the three tests done are all different, none can be said to be a reliable test of Mr. Barnard’s field of vision. In my opin­ion, from the results of this test, it would be difficult to rate Mr. Barnard with any permanent impairment as a result of the on-the-job injury.</blockquote>
                <p id="b87-7" pgmap="87">
                   The impairment rating given by Dr. Wallace does not address the claimant’s vision as corrected with glasses. Arkansas Code Annotated § 11-9-521(1987) addresses compensation for scheduled permanent injuries. Subsection (c) states, “In all cases of permanent loss of vision, the use of corrective lenses may be taken into consideration in evaluating the extent of loss of vision.” Dr. Gulley stated that the claimant’s corrected vision was normal.</p>
                <p id="b87-8" pgmap="87(115) 88(34)">
                   The Commission found that the claimant had not sustained his burden of proof by a preponderance of the credible evidence of record, and found that the claimant had not sustained any permanent disability as a result of his admittedly compens­able injury. The Commission has the duty of weighing medical evidence as it does any other evidence, and the resolution of any conflicts in the medical evidence is a question of fact for the Commission. Bartlett v. Mead Containerboard, 47 Ark. App. 181, 888 S.W.2d 314 (1994). The Commission is not required to believe the testimony of the claimant or any other witness, but may accept and translate into findings of fact only those portions of the testimony it deems worthy of belief. Jackson v. Circle T. Express, 49 Ark. App. 94, 896 S.W.2d 602 (1995). We conclude that the findings of the Commission are supported by substantial evidence.</p>
                <p id="b88-6" pgmap="88">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="83" ORDERLABEL="61" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00042_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00042_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_83.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="84" ORDERLABEL="62" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00042_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00042_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_84.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="85" ORDERLABEL="63" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00043_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00043_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_85.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="86" ORDERLABEL="64" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00043_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00043_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_86.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="87" ORDERLABEL="65" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00044_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00044_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_87.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="88" ORDERLABEL="66" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00044_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00044_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00044_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_88.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b84-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_84.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b87-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_87.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b85-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_85.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b85-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_85.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b85-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_85.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b83-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_83.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b83-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_83.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b83-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_83.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_87.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Amo" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_83.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AqF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_84.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_84.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_85.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AIC" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_83.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b84-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_84.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b84-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_84.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00042_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b88-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_88.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b87-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_87.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b87-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_87.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b86-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_86.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00043_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b87-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_87.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_88.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b88-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0011"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_88.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00044_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
