<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000676_0023" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Wackenhut Corp. v. Jones">WACKENHUT CORPORATION and St. Paul Fire &amp; Marine Ins. Co. v. Geneva Marchelle JONES</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 00-865</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">73 Ark. App. 158</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">40 S.W.3d 333</citation>
          <decisiondate>2001-03-21</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-23T00:52:59Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:06:04Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T13:32:03Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T13:34:47Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00092_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7b9a0263454d8e34fc8d3424088cf6ad" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="8752">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00092_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00093_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="033eade3350491ce0e80e8b62338a776" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="33598">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00093_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00093_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9ff0ed36dea102fa16a3b3b809bfe80c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="62560">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00093_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00094_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="22c58a0c599cbaa3d9a3a39231bbcae8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="42654">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00094_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00094_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="9589615444488b849858cde60cc21eb0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="50008">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00094_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00092_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="8f479829d6dd7dec10179e755d89c9f3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1493717">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00092_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00093_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="1a9da8f4811ea07fb70cee184caea59a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2355421">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00093_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00093_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="3d25aa221c2dffc0b47602c7bf9f4fb9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2809795">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00093_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00094_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0b2c1cbe5b3b2450978e9ba1bfdd133a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2676876">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00094_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00094_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0e9eb2f12766bd3b8323c243f852431b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2767774">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000676_00094_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00092_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f6d968f8526059545e9cbabd828e38a3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="10084">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000676_redacted_ALTO_00092_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00093_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d64011dbb21668748b382e0249391166" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54011">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000676_redacted_ALTO_00093_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00093_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3c12791751ad3a66b96221838599b8a7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="105742">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000676_redacted_ALTO_00093_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00094_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3bc74742947d03658d14cecbecb5e33e" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="74116">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000676_redacted_ALTO_00094_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00094_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6898b299cd1fbe01a65b5e52f9ae796c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="89846">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000676_redacted_ALTO_00094_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0023" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="158" lastpage="162">
              <court id="b184-5" pgmap="184">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division III</court>
              <docketnumber id="b184-4" pgmap="184">CA 00-865</docketnumber>
              <citation id="A8bi" pgmap="184">40 S.W.3d 333</citation>
              <parties id="b184-3" pgmap="184">WACKENHUT CORPORATION and St. Paul Fire &amp; Marine Ins. Co. v. Geneva Marchelle JONES</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b184-6" pgmap="184">Opinion delivered March 21, 2001</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b188-11" pgmap="188">Jennings and Neal, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b185-7" pgmap="185">Chisenhall, Nestrud, &amp; Julian, P.A., by: Jim L. Julian and Marck W. Hodge, for appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b185-8" pgmap="185">McCormick Law Firm, PA., by: David H. McCormick, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b185-9" pgmap="185">John F. STROUD, Jr., Chief Judge.</author>
                <p id="AgF" pgmap="185">Appellants, Wackenhut Corporation and St. Paul Fire &amp; Marine Insurance Com­pany, appeal the Workers’ Compensation Commission’s determina­tion that appellee Geneva Marchelle Jones’s left knee replacement was a reasonable and necessary consequence of her compensable injury under Ark. Code Ann. § ll-9-508(a) (Repl. 1996). We affirm.</p>
                <p id="b185-10" pgmap="185">Appellee, a security guard employed through appellants at Arkansas Nuclear One, sustained a compensable injury on Novem­ber 21, 1996, when she slipped on the wet running board of a truck and fell, injuring her left knee. She was treated conservatively by Dr. Terry Green, an orthopedic surgeon, and released to return to work on December 2, 1996.</p>
                <p id="b185-11" pgmap="185">Appellee continued to experience pain after her return to work, and she was referred to Dr. James Mulhollan, an orthopedic surgeon specializing in arthroscopic knee surgery, in April 1997. Dr. Mulhollan performed surgery on appellee’s left knee on April 14, 1997, and performed a second surgery on the left knee<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> on July 1, 1998.</p>
                <p id="b186-5" pgmap="186">Appellee returned to work on July 15, 1998, and worked on limited duty status until October 21, 1998, when she tripped on a mat at work and strained her knee again. Appellee did not return to work after this injury, and Dr. Barry Sorrells performed total knee replacements on both knees on March 2, 1999.</p>
                <p id="b186-6" pgmap="186">Appellee made a claim against appellants for the left knee replacement surgery, which appellants refused to pay. The adminis­trative law judge denied appellee’s claim; however, the Commission reversed that decision and awarded appellee benefits. Appellants now appeal, arguing that the surgery was not a reasonable and necessary consequence of appellee’s compensable injury.</p>
                <p id="b186-7" pgmap="186">
                   The standard of review in workers’ compensation cases is well-settled. We view the evidence and all reasonable inferences deducible therefrom in the light most favorable to the Commis­sion’s findings and affirm the decision if it is supported by substan­tial evidence. Geo Specialty Chem. v. Clingan, 69 Ark. App. 369, 13 S.W.3d 218 (2000). Substantial evidence is such relevant evidence as a reasonable mind might accept as adequate to support a conclu­sion. Air Compressor Equip. v. Sword, 69 Ark. App. 162, 11 S.W.3d 1 (2000). The issue is not whether we might have reached a different result or whether the evidence would have supported a contrary finding; if reasonable minds could reach the Commission’s conclu­sion, we must affirm its decision. Geo Specialty, supra. What consti­tutes reasonable and necessary medical treatment is a question of fact for the Commission. Green Bay Packaging v. Bartlett, 67 Ark. App. 332, 999 S.W.2d 695 (1999). When the primary injury is shown to have arisen out of and in the course of the employment, the employer is responsible for any natural consequence that flows from that injury; the basic test is whether there is a causal connec­tion between the two episodes. Jeter v. B.R. McGinty Mech., 62 Ark. App. 53, 968 S.W.2d 645 (1998).</p>
                <p id="b186-8" pgmap="186(127) 187(31)">In its decision, the Commission relied upon the deposition testimony of Dr. Mulhollan in awarding benefits to appellee. In his deposition, Dr. Mulhollan testified that appellee was bowlegged, which caused the load on the inner part of her knee to be dramati­cally higher than it is in the outer compartment of the knee. This condition is known as varus degeneration, which is an angular degenerative process, and it is the cause of most knee failures in females in their fifties, sixties, and seventies; however, appellee was in her early forties at the time of her knee replacements. He testified that when he first saw appellee in April 1997, her left knee, on a scale of one to four, with four being the worst, was probably a grade one, and her right knee was already a grade two or three. However, by January 1999, both knees had degenerated to a four-­plus level, which necessitated the double-knee replacement.</p>
                <p id="b187-6" pgmap="187">Dr. Mulhollan unequivocally stated that appellee’s compensa-­ble injury was the start of the rapid deterioration of appellee’s knee, that it was “probably predestined that this was going to occur, and the job injury just happened to be what triggered this one knee.” When asked whether the deterioration would have taken place as quickly without the job injury, Dr. Mulhollan replied, “That would be a purely speculative guess, because under my very eyes the opposite knee had the same process occur. So it may well have been predestined that it was going to occur, it just so happened that the job injury started the process on the left side.” When asked by appellants’ attorney whether it was his belief that the job injury probably exacerbated or accelerated the need for treatment of appellee’s condition, Dr. Mulhollan replied, “That’s correct.” On redirect examination, the following dialogue occurred between Dr. Mulhollan and appellee’s counsel:</p>
                <blockquote id="b187-7" pgmap="187">Appellee’s Counsel:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-8" pgmap="187">In terms of when [appellee] would have probably faced this [knee replacement] in the future had not this injury occurred, what, in your opinion — when would this have probably mani­fested itself to a degree that she would have had that knee replacement?</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-9" pgmap="187">Dr. Mulhollan:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-10" pgmap="187">You know, I can’t imagine. I think —. All I can really say is that it just probably occurred sooner.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-11" pgmap="187">Appellee’s Counsel:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-12" pgmap="187">Any figure, in your best professional judgment, of how much sooner because of the job-related injury?</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-13" pgmap="187">Dr. Mulhollan:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-14" pgmap="187">Probably the best guesstimate of how to come up with that number would have to be based on the —. By January of 1999, both knees had reached a 4+ degenerative level.</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b187-15" pgmap="187">Appellee’s Counsel:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b188-5" pgmap="188">That’s the most severe?</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b188-6" pgmap="188">Dr. Mulhollan:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b188-7" pgmap="188">That’s as bad as it can be. And this, of course, is when I referred her to Dr. Sorrells to have total replacement or osteotomy. But in any event, one knee had an injury and one knee didn’t have an injury prior to that, and they both ended up at the same level at the same time. So, you know, I guess I really —. The only timeta­ble I can give you is that I think it happened quicker than it probably would have without the job injury, but probably not a wide time span different.</blockquote>
                <p id="b188-8" pgmap="188">Appellants contend that our supreme court’s decisions in Crudup v. Regal Ware, Inc., 341 Ark. 804, 20 S.W.3d 900 (2000), and Frances v. Gaylord Container Corp., 341 Ark. 527, 20 S.W.3d 280 (2000), mandate reversal of the Commission’s decision. In Frances, supra, the supreme court held that “expert opinions based upon ‘could,’ ‘may,’ or ‘possibly’ lack the definiteness required to meet the claimant’s burden to prove causation pursuant to section 11 — 9— 102(16)(B).” 341 Ark. at 533, 20 S.W.3d at 284. This same rationale was employed by the supreme court one month later in Crudup, supra. We disagree with appellant’s argument that the language in Frances and Crudup require reversal in the case presently before us.</p>
                <p id="b188-9" pgmap="188">
                   An expert opinion is to be judged upon the entirety of the opinion, and it is not validated or invalidated on the presence or lack of “magic words.” Tyson Foods, Inc. v. Griffin, 61 Ark. App. 222, 966 S.W.2d 914 (1998). In the present case, Dr. Mulhollan stated that the job injury began the deterioration process in appel­lee’s left knee, and that the need for the total left knee replacement probably occurred sooner as a result of the compensable job injury. “Probably” is defined in The American Heritage Dictionary, New College Edition, as “most likely,” and it was not expressly prohib­ited by the supreme court’s decisions in Frances and Crudup, supra. We hold that use of the word “probably” is sufficient to satisfy the requirement of Ark. Code Ann. § 11-9-102(16) (B) (Supp. 1999) that medical opinions addressing compensability must be stated within a reasonable degree of medical certainty.</p>
                <p id="b188-10" pgmap="188">Affirmed.</p>
                <footnote label="1">
                  <p id="b185-12" pgmap="185">1 Dr. Mulhollan performed surgery on appellee’s right knee in October 1997; however, this surgery was not work related and is not the subject of this appeal.</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="184" ORDERLABEL="158" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00092_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00092_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_184.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="185" ORDERLABEL="159" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00093_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00093_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_185.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="186" ORDERLABEL="160" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00093_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00093_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_186.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="187" ORDERLABEL="161" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00094_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00094_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_187.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="188" ORDERLABEL="162" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00094_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00094_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_188.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AgF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b184-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b186-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_186.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A8bi" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_184.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00092_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b185-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_185.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00093_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b187-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_187.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b188-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0023"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_188.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00094_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
