<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000684_0015" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Cottrell v. Beard">Lucille Beard COTTRELL, Pearl Beard Crawford, and Virginia Beard Abbott v. Pauline BEARD; Jimmy Beard and Thelma Beard, Husband and Wife; and Bob Launius and Letitia Launius, Husband and Wife</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 99-731</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">69 Ark. App. 87</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">9 S.W.3d 568</citation>
          <decisiondate>2000-02-02</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T00:48:51Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:11:22Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-19T10:39:02Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-19T10:40:12Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170715.post179</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00058_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0ef5a0b6f8cd0cd7866125ac1474d0fa" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="17764">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00058_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00058_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="30b764a89b64d18f388ef016379437f8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34248">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00058_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00059_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7b4811aa0d27393fcb6ff514689f5f33" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="59186">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00059_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00059_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="889a0ce8a105616e866db99f9727c52c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="58462">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00059_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00060_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="f104bf86080d4a57428ed38575de79fc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="55476">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00060_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00060_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="01e4bfcf7b944a902c2b331fbc5321a9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="10920">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00060_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00058_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6017e6b0e9885c36724701489259ff65" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1849137">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00058_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00058_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="4377e1ac95bda8ed8ccf82108ae75ce9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2106342">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00058_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00059_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="fdd86a8195d8e03309028a31cd71375d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2689929">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00059_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00059_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0772e5374b5532b10fbb945b6138fdc5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2665227">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00059_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00060_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="70979ea073144ffe0b39192cc052f513" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2640164">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00060_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00060_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="240993026027889ef4a12d041b518dd9" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1610406">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000684_00060_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00058_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d74ddf2c514427cf51e5ff8cedc3d88c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="24927">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00058_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00058_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="08f883e8a50a927441eb41bbfac081df" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="56522">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00058_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00059_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="bfe46499cae0f683fbd7708c9bfd1013" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="100770">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00059_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00059_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4a092562e6e0b953d89a6b9e1f55978d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="103758">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00059_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00060_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="168c8ef19eb4fa4bfd40b43da7f08856" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="96696">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00060_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00060_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d418c31567d35aeb3554aa1df3bdf97c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="15447">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000684_redacted_ALTO_00060_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0015" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="87" lastpage="92">
              <court pgmap="115" id="b115-10">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division III</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="115" id="b115-9">CA 99-731</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="115" id="Adz">9 S.W.3d 568</citation>
              <parties pgmap="115" id="b115-7">Lucille Beard COTTRELL, Pearl Beard Crawford, and Virginia Beard Abbott v. Pauline BEARD; Jimmy Beard and Thelma Beard, Husband and Wife; and Bob Launius and Letitia Launius, Husband and Wife</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="115" id="b115-11">Opinion delivered February 2, 2000</decisiondate>
              <judges pgmap="120" id="b120-5">Rogers and Meads, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="116" id="b116-8">Tim A. Womack, P.A., by: Michael W. Frey, for appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="116" id="b116-9">Phillip J. Foster, for appellees.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="116" id="b116-10">John B. Robbins, Chief Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="116" id="A2l">This is an appeal from a decision denying appellants’ attempt to enforce a reservation to repurchase an interest in land set forth in a 1961 deed. We affirm the chancellor’s decision on the basis that the reservation is inappli­cable to the situation before us.</p>
                <p pgmap="116" id="b116-11">On September 16, 1961, appellants, Lucille Beard Cottrell, Pearl Beard Crawford, and Virginia Beard Abbott, along with their five cotenants, conveyed their individual undivided 1/16 interests in land in Ouachita County to their cotenants and siblings, Ola Beard Meadows and John Carroll Beard. This deed contained the follow­ing language: “also reserving the right of opportunity to purchase said lands in case Grantees desire to sell the same at and for the best price of any bona fide offer.” Appellants are the surviving grantors to that deed. Between 1967 and 1976, Ola and John Carroll con­veyed several portions of the property to third parties without objection by appellants.</p>
                <p pgmap="116(58) 117(113)" id="b116-12">In April 1990, Ola, who owned an undivided 9/16 interest in the property prior to the September 1961 deed, but a 12/16 interest thereafter, conveyed all of her interest to John Carroll and his wife, appellee Pauline Beard. This deed was filed in April 1993. In June 1991, John Carroll and Pauline executed a deed to themselves to create an estate by the entirety. On July 25, 1992, John Carroll and Pauline deeded six acres to appellees Bob and Letitia Launius. This deed was recorded on October 14, 1992. It is undisputed that this conveyance was a gift, that the Launiuses gave no consideration for the deed, and that appellants did not have actual notice of the transaction before it occurred. John Carroll and Pauline gave appel-­lees Jimmy Beard and Thelma Beard a deed to 5.6 acres on July 12, 1993, without receiving any consideration and without giving actual notice to appellants. This deed was recorded on July 14, 1993. Ola and John Carroll died before this action was filed.</p>
                <p pgmap="117" id="b117-6">In 1994, appellant Lucille Cottrell, Pete Brazeale, and Bob Abbott initiated this action against Pauline, arguing that the deed from Ola to John Carroll and Pauline violated their right of first refusal set forth in the 1961 deed. In an amended complaint, Mr. Brazeale and Mr. Abbott were deleted as plaintiffs, appellants Pearl Beard Crawford and Virginia Beard Abbott were added as plaintiffs, and the Launiuses and the Beards were joined as defendants. Appel­lants also attacked the deeds to the Launiuses and the Beards and argued that they were entitled to enforce their right of first refusal. They contended that they should be declared the lawful owners of the property upon payment of the same consideration (nothing) given by the Beards and the Launknes. In the alternative, they asked the chancellor to cancel the deeds.</p>
                <p pgmap="117" id="b117-7">In a letter opinion dated December 31, 1998, the chancellor cited Broach v. City of Hampton, 283 Ark. 496, 677 S.W.2d 851 (1984), and stated that, because the reservation of a right to repur­chase is limited to the lives of the grantees, appellants had waited too long to enforce it. He also made the following findings:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="117" id="b117-8">Additionally, the Court declines to acknowledge the unilat­eral reservation of the right to repurchase as being viable. The six grantors in that certain deed of September 16, 1961, owned an undivided 1/16th, each, interest in the property they were convey­ing to the grantees. The Plaintiffs in this action collectively owned an undivided 3/16th interest in the property in issue. They argue that they should be able to effect a reversion to them of their undivided fractional share in the property, which is now vested in the Defendant, Pauline Beard. This, I submit to you, is an unrea­sonable restraint on alienation and is against public policy. For this additional reason, Plaintiffs’ complaint and amended complaint should be denied and dismissed.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="118" id="b118-5">Throughout the briefing and pleading in this case, the parties erroneously refer to the reservation set forth in the deed of Sep­tember 16, 1961 as an “option.” It is not an option to repurchase. It is a reservation of the right to repurchase. The grantees in that deed never formally acknowledged the reservation as an option.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="118" id="b118-6">The chancellor found that Ola’s deed to John Carroll and Pauline was a gift and noted that the parties had stipulated that the deeds to the Launiuses and Beards were given as gifts and without considera­tion. He then stated: “Thus, they do not meet the criteria for the reservation Plaintiffs assert, as there is not a bona fide offer.” He entered an order incorporating these findings and dismissing appel­lants’ complaint on February 22, 1999.</p>
                <p pgmap="118" id="b118-7">On appeal, appellants argue the following three points: (1) the chancellor erred in finding that the reserved right of first refusal terminated at the death of the grantees; (2) the chanceEor erred in finding the reservation to be an unlawful restraint on the alienation of land; and (3) the chancellor erred in holding that the right of first refusal had not been “triggered” because the conveyances were gifts and there had been no bona fide offer. We need not address the first two points because we affirm on the ground that the reservation had no application to the facts of this case.</p>
                <p pgmap="118" id="b118-8">Appellants agree that all of the conveyances at issue were gifts; further, they have not argued that the chancellor’s finding that there was no bona fide offer is clearly erroneous. Instead, they assert that a gift of the property is equal to a sale of it for a fair price. They state that, even though the conveyances were gifts and without consider­ation, the “decision to transfer the property ... still triggered the appellants’ preemptive rights.” In response, appellees correctly point out that appellants have cited no case or other authority that sup­ports this assertion. Appellants also argue that, if the chancellor’s decision is affirmed, “the grantee in an instrument containing pre­emptive rights can circumvent such rights immediately after acquir­ing the property. The grantee need merely use a straw man.”</p>
                <p pgmap="118(73) 119(97)" id="b118-9">
                   The right on which appellants rely was created by res­ervation in the 1961 deed. A reservation is a clause in a deed whereby the grantor reserves some new thing to himself, issuing out of the thing granted which was not in esse before. Wallner v. Johnson, 21 Ark. App. 124, 730 S.W.2d 253 (1987). The right reserved in the deed in question is not strictly an option, as the chancellor noted; it is usually referred to as a preemptive right or a right of first refusal. Estate of Johnson v. Carr, 288 Ark. 461, 706 S.W.2d 388 (1986). This right is based on a condition precedent and ordinarily promises that, before offering the property for sale or accepting an offer from another, the owner will first offer the property to the holder of the right at the offered price or at some predetermined price. Id. The chancellor’s finding as to whether the necessary condition precedent has occurred will not be reversed on appeal unless it is clearly erroneous. Id.</p>
                <p pgmap="119" id="b119-6">
                   When the court is called upon to construe a deed, we will examine it from its four corners for the purpose of ascertaining the parties’ intent from the language employed and will not resort to rules of construction when the deed is clear and contains no ambiguities. See Gibson v. Pickett, 256 Ark. 1035, 512 S.W.2d 532 (1974); Winningham v. Harris, 64 Ark. App. 239, 981 S.W.2d 540 (1998). A reservation will be given effect according to the plain meaning and intent of the language used and cannot be extended beyond its terms. 26 C.J.S. Deeds § 140(1) (1956).</p>
                <p pgmap="119" id="b119-7">
                   We simply cannot agree with appellants’ contention that the reservation in question, which applies only if the grantees wish to sell the property, can reasonably be read as applying to a gift. A sale is a contract by which one party transfers the ownership of property to another for a price. Black’s Law Dictionary 1337 (7th ed. 1999). A gift is a voluntary transfer of property, without valua­ble consideration, to another. Davis v. Jackson, 232 Ark. 953, 341 S.W.2d 762 (1961). Therefore, this reservation unambiguously fails to provide appellants with a right of first refusal in the context of a gift. Accordingly, we affirm the chancellor’s decision on this basis.</p>
                <p pgmap="119" id="b119-8">As to appellants’ argument that a grantor’s rights under these circumstances can be easily thwarted by the grantee simply convey­ing to a straw man, we note that there is no evidence here that appellees were mere straw persons through whom title was to pass on to someone else for consideration. Furthermore, we are confi­dent that, in a case where there is some evidence of this, it would be a matter for the trial court to look through the form of a transaction to determine whether a purported gift is in fact a gift or a subter­fuge to conceal a sale.</p>
                <p pgmap="119" id="b119-9">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="115" ORDERLABEL="87" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00058_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00058_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_115.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="116" ORDERLABEL="88" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00058_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00058_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_116.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="117" ORDERLABEL="89" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00059_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00059_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_117.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="118" ORDERLABEL="90" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00059_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00059_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_118.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="119" ORDERLABEL="91" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00060_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00060_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_119.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="120" ORDERLABEL="92" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00060_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00060_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00060_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_120.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b118-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_118.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b118-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_118.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Adz" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_115.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b118-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_118.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b118-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_118.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_119.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b120-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_120.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b116-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b116-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b115-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_115.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b119-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_119.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A2l" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b119-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_119.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b119-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_119.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b115-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_115.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b117-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_117.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b119-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_119.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00060_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b118-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_118.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b116-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b116-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b116-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_116.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_117.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b115-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_115.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b115-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_115.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00058_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b117-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_117.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b117-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0015"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_117.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00059_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
