<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000717_0018" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Miller v. State">Roger Lee MILLER v. STATE of Arkansas</name>
          <docketnumber>CA CR 92-1028</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">44 Ark. App. 112</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">868 S.W.2d 510</citation>
          <decisiondate>1993-12-15</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-21T16:28:10Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:40:16Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:22:21Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:22:43Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00067_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="7680c5e9b88d234040114c6e77ee90bc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="18154">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00067_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00068_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="646d56696c1a12121ee5268e40d8e074" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="51234">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00068_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00068_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ddc248cfcb512e3384cb63fe0a442d9c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="50568">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00068_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00069_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="4b6e8c98db555ceed0cab0febe6befb0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="53792">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00069_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00069_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e0133c5bb737bafcfa4f9e92a30f4a39" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="55404">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00069_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00067_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="1fb377c1d8a5ca6f94e81f16c065ffc5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1683290">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00067_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00068_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="047c99becbbf3e9b8daa4f29e78e7617" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2517983">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00068_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00068_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="df6f39e1294c0c9a9081b799d18a5bc4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2938320">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00068_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00069_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="f3bdd55cbb55a3ee721016cfb36c2615" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2772432">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00069_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00069_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6f0b116233a39f7c4a326c7c68837ba7" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2555786">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00069_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00067_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="552b0cf2afaf62d3dcb8fc0ba2a1ac7c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="27232">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00067_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00068_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c6e00eb2b5357446613cb5cb0e249b2c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86104">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00068_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00068_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e6e6612dabb2d73a9e5d64acedf715b4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="89450">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00068_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00069_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1820a2f532e116df18536e3741e06146" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="95118">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00069_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00069_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="34dda6124c3b8f1ba2de90106d49167b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="100338">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00069_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0018" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="112" lastpage="116">
              <court id="b134-4" pgmap="134">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber id="A8m" pgmap="134">CA CR 92-1028</docketnumber>
              <citation id="Abs" pgmap="134">868 S.W.2d 510</citation>
              <parties id="b134-3" pgmap="134">Roger Lee MILLER v. STATE of Arkansas</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b134-5" pgmap="134">Opinion delivered December 15, 1993</decisiondate>
              <otherdate id="b134-6" pgmap="134">[Rehearing denied January 19, 1994.]</otherdate>
              <judges id="b138-9" pgmap="138">Robbins and Mayfield, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b134-14" pgmap="134">Paul Petty and Robert Meurer, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b134-15" pgmap="134">Winston Bryant, Att’y Gen., by: Gil Dudley, Asst. Att’y Gen., for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b134-16" pgmap="134">John E. Jennings, Chief Judge.</author>
                <p id="ANS" pgmap="134(45) 135(25)">Roger Miller was charged with possession of a controlled substance (cocaine) with intent to deliver and driving on a suspended driver’s license. After a pretrial motion to suppress evidence was denied, Miller entered a conditional plea of guilty under Ark. R. Crim. R 24.3(b). He was sentenced to twenty-five years imprisonment with ten years suspended on the drug charge, and was fined $500.00 for dri­ving on a suspended license.</p>
                <p id="b135-6" pgmap="135">The primary argument on appeal is that the trial court erred in not finding that Miller’s arrest was pretéxtual and therefore erred in not suppressing the evidence obtained as the result of the arrest. We find no error and affirm.</p>
                <p id="b135-7" pgmap="135">The facts are not in dispute. Most of the testimony at the sup­pression hearing was provided by Roger Ahlf, an Arkansas state police officer, who worked as a narcotics investigator. In Decem­ber of 1991, Ahlf was working with David Drennan, a narcotics investigator for the Searcy Regional Drug Task Force. During that time Ahlf and Drennan were told by a confidential infor­mant that the appellant was a cocaine dealer. Ahlf was also told by the confidential informant that appellant was driving a black van on a suspended driver’s license, and Ahlf verified this infor­mation.</p>
                <p id="b135-8" pgmap="135">On December 18, 1991, Officer Ahlf stopped the appellant for driving on a suspended driver’s license. Ahlf testified that he normally did not work traffic, that he wrote only two or three tickets per year, and that he stopped the appellant in hopes that he would find drugs. He testified that he frisked the appellant for weapons, that he knew appellant to be a drug user, and that he knew that people who use cocaine carry razor blades. In the course of the search of appellant’s person, Ahlf found an address book containing marijuana residue, described as “probably less than I-V2 of a gram.” Miller was taken into custody and the offi­cer’s search of the van turned up a plastic bag containing cocaine!</p>
                <p id="b135-9" pgmap="135">The circuit court in denying the motion to suppress said, “While Investigator Ahlf may have had motives in addition to a traffic stop, the evidence does not establish that the arrest would not have been made but for the drug and search interest of Inves­tigator Ahlf.”</p>
                <p id="b135-10" pgmap="135">Appellant relies primarily on Richardson v. State, 288 Ark. 407, 706 S.W.2d 363 (1986). There, the supreme court quoted from McKnight v. United States, 183 F.2d 977 (D.C. Cir. 1950):</p>
                <blockquote id="b136-5" pgmap="136">The Supreme Court has specifically held that “an arrest may not be used as a pretext to search for evidence.” Unit­ed States v. Lefkowitz, 285 U.S. 452 (1932). ... It is set­tled law that “when it appears, as it does here, that the search and not the arrest was the real object of the offi­cers in entering upon the premises, and that the arrest was a pretext for or at the most an incident of the search,” the search was not reasonable within the meaning of the Con­stitution. Henderson v. United States, 12 F.2d 528 (4th Cir. 1926).</blockquote>
                <p id="b136-6" pgmap="136">Appellant also notes the supreme court’s approval of a statement found in Brown v. State, 442 N.E.2d 1109 (Ind. 1982), that “the issue of pretext arrest only arises when the surrounding circum­stances show that the arrest is only a sham being used as an excuse for making a search for evidence of a different and more serious offense for which no probable cause exists.”</p>
                <p id="b136-7" pgmap="136">While it is true that the issue of pretextual arrest was the sub­ject of extended discussion in Richardson, it would seem that the real basis for the court’s holding was a violation of the deten­tion limits imposed by Rule 3.1 of the Arkansas Rules of Crim­inal Procedure. The court in Richardson said, “Regardless of whether we can technically justify the arrest on the charge of public intoxication, we can find no justification whatever for these rules violations.”</p>
                <p id="b136-8" pgmap="136">
                   Shortly after the decision in Richardson, the supreme court decided Hines v. State, 289 Ark. 50, 709 S.W.2d 65 (1986). After distinguishing Richardson, the court, in a unanimous deci­sion, said:</p>
                <blockquote id="b136-9" pgmap="136(101) 137(71)">Claims of pretextual arrest raise a unique problem in the law — deciding whether an ulterior motive prompted an arrest which otherwise would not have occurred. Con­fusion can be avoided by applying a “but for” approach, that is, would the arrest not have occurred but for the other, typically the more serious, crime. Where the police have a dual motive in making an arrest, what might be termed the covert motive is not tainted by the overt motive, even though the covert motive may be dominant, so long as the arrest would have been carried out had the covert motive been absent. Professor LaFave, Criminal Procedure, § 3.1(d), p. 144, describes this as the correct result. Because the action would have been taken in any event, he states, “[T]here is no conduct which ought to have been deterred and, thus, no reason to bring the Fourth Amendment exclu­sionary rule into play.” Abel v. United States, 362 U.S. 217 (1966). See People v. Guido, 95 Misc.2d 47, 407 NYS 2130 (1978).</blockquote>
                <p id="b137-6" pgmap="137">See also, Ray v. State, 304 Ark. 489, 803 S.W.2d 894 (1991). As the decision in Hines at least implies, the test should be an objec­tive one. Virtually all courts that have recently considered the question agree. See, e.g., United States v. Rivera, 906 F.2d 319 (7th Cir. 1990) (an officer’s subjective intent is irrelevant); Unit­ed States v. Trigg, 925 F.2d 1064 (7th Cir. 1991); United States v. Rivera, 867 F.2d 1261 (10th Cir. 1989); (an objective analysis of the facts and circumstances of a pretextual stop is appropriate, rather than an inquiry into the officer’s subjective intent); Unit­ed States v. Guzman, 864 F.2d 1512 (10th Cir. 1988); United States v. Causey, 834 F.2d 1179 (5th Cir. 1987); United States v. Gallo, 927 F.2d 815 (5th Cir. 1991); United States v. Bates, 840 F.2d 858 (11th Cir. 1988); State v. Mease, 842 S.W.2d 98 (Mo. 1992); State v. Olsen, 482 N.W.2d 212 (Minn. 1992); State v. Garcia, 461 N.W.2d 460 (Iowa 1991). These decisions and oth­ers are based, at least in part, on statements made by the United States Supreme Court. In Scott v. United States, 436 U.S. 128 (1978), the Supreme Court said that police searches are to be test­ed “under a standard of objective reasonableness without regard to the underlying intent or motivation of the officers involved.” In Horton v. California, 496 U.S. 128 (1990), the Court said that “evenhanded law enforcement is best achieved by the application of objective standards of conduct, rather than standards that depend upon the subjective state of mind of the officer.” Professor LaFave puts it this way:</p>
                <blockquote id="AcK" pgmap="137">Likewise, if the police stop X’s car for minor offense A, and they “subjectively hoped to discover contraband during the stop” so as to establish serious offense B, the stop is nonethe­less lawful if “a reasonable officer would have made the stop in the absence of the invalid purpose.”</blockquote>
                <p id="b137-8" pgmap="137(12) 138(54)">1 Wayne R. LaFave, Search and Seizure (Supp. 1994 at 22). We conclude that this is the test to be applied.<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> We think this test is consonant with the most recent decisions of the Arkansas Supreme Court in Hines and Ray, and with the statements of the United States Supreme Court in Horton v. California. It was also the test utilized by the trial court here.</p>
                <p id="b138-6" pgmap="138">
                   In the case at bar it is quite clear that Officer Ahlf’s primary purpose in stopping appellant was to search for drugs. As the. supreme court said in Hines, however, the arrest is not “taint­ed” by this fact “so long as the arrest would have been carried out” anyway. We think that the trial court’s finding that the arrest would have occurred in any event is not clearly erroneous. The test is whether a “reasonable officer” would have made the traffic stop — not whether this particular officer would have made the stop absent his ulterior motive. The Constitution does not prohibit offi­cers assigned to work on particular types of offenses to refrain from arresting those who commit offenses outside the officers’ area of specialty.</p>
                <p id="b138-7" pgmap="138">
                   If, as we have held, the stop and arrest of the appel­lant was valid, there remains the question of the validity of the subsequent search. Officer Ahlf characterized the search as both an “inventory” and as a search incident to arrest. Our decision on this point is clearly governed by New York v. Belton, 450 U.S. 1028 (1981). There the Court held that when a policeman has made a lawful custodial arrest of the occupants of an automobile, he may, as a contemporaneous incident of that arrest, search the pas­senger compartment of that automobile. See also, Campbell v. State, 294 Ark. 639, 746 S.W.2d 37 (1988); Williams v. State, 4 Ark. App. 24, 627 S.W.2d 28 (1982). Because this was a valid search incident to arrest under Belton we need not reach the issue of whether a valid inventory was conducted. See Stevens v. State, 38 Ark. App. 209, 832 S.W.2d 275 (1992).</p>
                <p id="b138-8" pgmap="138">For the reasons stated the decision of the trial court is affirmed.</p>
                <footnote label="1">
                  <p id="b138-10" pgmap="138">1 The Eighth Circuit Court of Appeals has held that the test is whether the officer could validly have made the stop and that “so long as the police are doing no more than they are legally permitted and objectively authorized to so, [the resulting stop or] arrest is constitutional.” United States v. Cummins, 920 F.2d 498 (8th Cir. 1990) (quot­ing United States v. Trigg, 878 F.2d 1037 (7th Cir. 1989)).</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="134" ORDERLABEL="112" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00067_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00067_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_134.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="135" ORDERLABEL="113" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00068_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00068_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_135.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="136" ORDERLABEL="114" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00068_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00068_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_136.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="137" ORDERLABEL="115" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00069_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00069_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_137.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="138" ORDERLABEL="116" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00069_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00069_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_138.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A8m" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b135-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AcK" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_137.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b138-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b138-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b137-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_137.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b135-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b135-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b135-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b136-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_136.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b136-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_136.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b136-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_136.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b136-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_136.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_137.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="ANS" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b137-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_137.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b135-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_135.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b134-15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b138-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b138-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b138-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_138.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00069_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Abs" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_134.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00067_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b136-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0018"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_136.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00068_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
