<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000699_0063" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Clarendon National Insurance v. Roberts">CLARENDON NATIONAL INSURANCE COMPANY v. Stanley ROBERTS and Rick Turman</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 02-1205</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">82 Ark. App. 515</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">120 S.W.3d 141</citation>
          <decisiondate>2003-06-18</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-21T17:01:06Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:24:47Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T10:16:21Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-17T10:20:32Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00268_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="d9a98744c7298153dd291fbccb9da274" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="27948">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00268_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00268_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="87137b994e68cb43ada6fdd00e720493" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="3864">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00268_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00269_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="0519590b9c5ce562ff8b88968fdc4ed8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="48392">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00269_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00269_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a91a01a2be69f117fd1a27558589396b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="42982">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00269_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00270_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="15c32d76e83950fc22aed6b08ca99cdc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54086">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00270_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00270_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="83b914b4c53c55ccbe34cf5767558ac1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="39146">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00270_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00268_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0c92733af96a1767fde6ebb9fb00fdf1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2071334">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00268_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00268_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="f9f82f21c976508691d9f5c265a23dd4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1042505">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00268_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00269_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6ab47c6349d439f103b222e02bca3cc0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2508291">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00269_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00269_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="cea03c89353ab10522107988e7c5dad4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2444440">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00269_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00270_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="d3e767c75f66cc74abf06cec50124649" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2506054">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00270_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00270_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="131ca65eaad8de0c7591ace47ef8524c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2417675">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000699_00270_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00268_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f3d41194bff4c93ed9de1e20d1d0d6ec" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="44063">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00268_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00268_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="4b54a1cad288994d404f544f9506e3a1" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1684">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00268_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00269_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3cc88797944039f35c78c5dea0a03756" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="76417">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00269_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00269_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="de40c1c8794fb3be5cb04ff242bddbba" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="75779">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00269_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00270_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="db064b8736af50c789c5a551e1e2b1cb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="91429">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00270_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00270_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="98db7790839d7570085956a56f06cb6d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="66404">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000699_redacted_ALTO_00270_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0063" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="520" firstpage="515">
              <court id="b535-7" pgmap="535">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division III</court>
              <docketnumber id="b535-6" pgmap="535">CA 02-1205</docketnumber>
              <citation id="Amo" pgmap="535">120 S.W.3d 141</citation>
              <parties id="b535-5" pgmap="535">CLARENDON NATIONAL INSURANCE COMPANY v. Stanley ROBERTS and Rick Turman</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b535-8" pgmap="535">Opinion delivered June 18, 2003</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b540-8" pgmap="540">Stroud, C.J., and Crabtree J., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="AWa" pgmap="537">Appeal from Crittenden Circuit Court; David Burnett, Judge; affirmed.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b537-4" pgmap="537">Reid, Burge, Prevallet &amp; Coleman, by: Richard A. Reid, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b537-5" pgmap="537">Woodruff Law Firm, P.A., by: Arlon L. Woodruff, for appellees.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="pAr4" pgmap="537">Olly Neal, Judge. Appellant,</author>
                <p id="AtYE" pgmap="537">Clarendon National Insurance Company, (Clarendon) appeals the grant of the appellees’, Stanley Roberts and Rick Turman, motion for summary judgment. Clarendon raises the following issues on appeal: (1) the trial court erred when it failed to find that the policy language was a condition precedent to coverage and that the appellees had failed to comply with the language of the pol­icy; (2) the trial court erred in finding that there was an enforceable insurance contract when the appellees failed to pay the insurance premium. We affirm.</p>
                <p id="b537-7" pgmap="537">The appellees own thoroughbred racing horses. Clarendon is an insurance company that issues animal mortality policies. The appellees had an animal mortality policy with Clarendon that pro­vided coverage for all of their animals. The policy also contained an automatic extension provision that provided for coverage of subsequently acquired animals.</p>
                <p id="b537-8" pgmap="537">On February 5, 2000, the appellees purchased a horse, “Ack-­adackadoo,” at a $20,000 claiming race. During the race, the horse was injured and had to be put to death that same day. The appellees notified Clarendon’s agent of the acquisition and loss on February 28, 2000. Clarendon denied coverage, contending that the terms of the automatic extension provision were not complied with, in that the appellees had failed to pay the premium on the new acquisition and failed to provide notice of the acquisition within five days of the actual acquisition. The appellees filed suit alleging that the policy provided automatic coverage. Both parties moved for summary judgment. Clarendon argued that compli­ance with the terms of the automatic extension provision was a condition precedent to coverage. The appellees argued that notice was irrelevant because the automatic extension provision provided for automatic coverage.</p>
                <p id="b538-2" pgmap="538">The trial court denied Clarendon’s motion for summary judg­ment and granted the appellees’ motion for summary judgment. The trial court found that the policy provided automatic coverage and awarded the appellees $20,000 for their loss. Clarendon only appeals the grant of the appellees’ motion for summary judgment.</p>
                <p id="b538-3" pgmap="538">
                   Normally, on a summary-judgment appeal, the evidence is viewed in the light most favorable to the party resisting the motion, and any doubts and inferences are resolved against the mov­ing party. Tunnel v. Progressive Northern Ins. Co., 80 Ark. App. 215, 95 S.W.3d 1 (2003). But in a case where the parties agree on the facts, we simply determine whether the appellee was entitled to judgment as a matter of law. Id. When parties file cross-motions for summary judgments, as was done in this case, they essentially agree that there are no material facts remaining, and summary judgment is an appropriate means of resolving the case. Id.</p>
                <p id="b538-4" pgmap="538">
                   The policy language at issue provides:</p>
                <blockquote id="b538-5" pgmap="538">C. AUTOMATIC EXTENSION FOR SECTION III COVERAGE</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-7" pgmap="538">1. If YOU insure all of YOUR animals (that YOU insure) with US, all animals subsequently acquired through claiming or bona fide auction will be covered automatically by this policy. OUR limit of liability for such animals will not exceed the lesser of:</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-8" pgmap="538">a. the claiming price or the final bid; or</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-9" pgmap="538">b. $50,000.00</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-10" pgmap="538">2. This amount of insurance</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-11" pgmap="538">a. will apply only to YOUR interest in the animal; and</blockquote>
                <blockquote id="b538-12" pgmap="538">b. is subject to OUR receiving notice that insur­ance is desired within 5 calendar days from time of acquisition, and in consideration of the pre­mium paid.</blockquote>
                <p id="b538-13" pgmap="538(46) 539(53)">(Emphasis added.) A cardinal rule of insurance law is that policies of insurance will be interpreted and construed liberally in favor of the insured and strictly against the insurer. Keller v. Safeco Ins. Co., 317 Ark. 308, 877 S.W.2d 90 (1994). Any ambiguity found in the insurance contract is to be construed against the insurer since the insurer wrote the policy without any consultation with the insured. Countryside Cas. Co. v. Grant, 269 Ark. 526, 601 S.W.2d 875 (1980). An ambiguity exists when a provision is susceptible to more than one reasonable interpretation. Keller v. Safeco Ins. Co., supra.</p>
                <p id="b539-4" pgmap="539">Clarendon argues that the failure to give notice of either the acquisition or loss of the horse within five days prevented any recovery under the policy. Clarendon further argues that compli­ance with the terms of the provision was a condition precedent to coverage. In contrast the appellees read the provision as providing automatic coverage for a period of five days following the acquisi­tion of an animal; they further interpret the language to read that notice of acquisition and loss is only necessary to support proof of loss and a demand for payment. The appellees also read the provi­sion as requiring them to notify Clarendon prior to expiration of the five-day automatic insurance period if they desire to extend coverage beyond the five-day period.</p>
                <p id="b539-5" pgmap="539">
                   The language in the provision here at issue is suscepti­ble to either interpretation; therefore, the language in the provi­sion is ambiguous. Thus, construing the language of the provision against Clarendon, we hold that under the facts herein, the horse was insured at the time of acquisition pursuant to the automatic insurance provision. The horse was also insured at the time of the loss, which was only a few minutes after the horse’s acquisition. At no time prior to the loss did the horse become uninsured.</p>
                <p id="b539-6" pgmap="539">
                   In Horace Mann Mutual Casualty Co. v. Bell, 134 F.Supp. 307 (W.D. Ark. 1955), the district court interpreted an automatic insurance provision involving newly acquired vehicles. The district court held that despite having partial coverage on the newly acquired vehicle with another company the insured was not precluded from having coverage under the automatic insurance policy that was at issue. The district court explained:</p>
                <blockquote id="b539-7" pgmap="539">[TJhere is nothing to require the insured to insure his newly acquired vehicles with the company in order to take advantage of the 30-day automatic insurance on the new vehicle. For that matter, he may wait 30 days, having free automatic insurance during that time, and then purchase insurance on the new vehicle from another company.</blockquote>
                <p id="b540-4" pgmap="540">Id. at 312. The provision at bar is analogous to an automatic insurance provision found in an automobile policy; therefore, appellees did not have to do anything to take advantage of the five-day automatic insurance coverage, and following the expira­tion of the five-day automatic insurance period, appellees were free to explore other insurance opportunities.</p>
                <p id="b540-5" pgmap="540">
                   Clarendon also argues that the trial court erred when it found there was an enforceable contract of insurance on the horse when the appellees had failed to tender an insurance premium. An insurance policy is a contract between the insurer and insured. Southern Farm Bureau Cas. Ins. Co. v. Craven, 79 Ark. App. 423, 89 S.W.3d 369 (2002). The premium is the consideration for the insurance. Farm Bureau P. H. v. FM. Bureau Mut. Ins. Co., 335 Ark. 285, 984 S.W.2d 6 (1998). In situations involving automatic insur­ance on vehicles, it has been said that the consideration is the pre­mium or premiums paid by the insured on his previously owned vehicles. Horace Mann Mut. Cas. Co. v. Bell, supra. As stated earlier, the present situation is analogous to that involving automatic insur­ance on a vehicle. Accordingly, the proper consideration was the premium or premiums paid by the appellees on their other animals. Therefore, the parties had an enforceable contract.</p>
                <p id="b540-6" pgmap="540">
                   We hold that the trial court did not err when it failed to find that the policy language was a condition precedent to cov­erage and when it found that there was an enforceable insurance contract. Therefore, the trial court’s grant of the appellees’ motion for summary judgment was proper, and we affirm.</p>
                <p id="b540-7" pgmap="540">Affirmed.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="535" ORDERLABEL="515" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00268_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00268_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_535.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="536" ORDERLABEL="516" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00268_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00268_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00268_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_536.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="537" ORDERLABEL="517" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00269_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00269_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_537.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="538" ORDERLABEL="518" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00269_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00269_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_538.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="539" ORDERLABEL="519" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00270_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00270_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_539.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="540" ORDERLABEL="520" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00270_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00270_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_540.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b540-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_540.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AWa" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b539-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_539.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b539-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_539.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b540-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_540.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b535-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_535.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b539-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_539.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AtYE" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b540-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_540.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b539-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_539.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b540-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_540.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Amo" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_535.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b537-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b537-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b537-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b535-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_535.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b538-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_538.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_539.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="pAr4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b540-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_540.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00270_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b535-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_535.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b537-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_537.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00269_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b535-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0063"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_535.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00268_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
