<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000717_0003" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Snisky v. Whisenhunt">Edward James SNISKY v. Sharon Kay WHISENHUNT</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 93-163</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">44 Ark. App. 13</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">864 S.W.2d 875</citation>
          <decisiondate>1993-11-03</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-21T16:28:10Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:40:16Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:22:21Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:22:43Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post176</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00018_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="03a76808ce9b82c8a33dd52486761bc5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="7820">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00018_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00018_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5937f80db832f789c1b646136e21785b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="36474">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00018_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="94732aa924123c3008cf10e110215364" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57862">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00019_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00019_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="09f9155d4eb4290f21c3a6840f3bc94a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="58756">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00019_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00020_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="3cd240c9251bd64260237131086e14cf" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="59794">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00020_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00020_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="d6cfe364c2569e4693178da831d1fa63" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="39746">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00020_1.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00018_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="0dc78aaf927b19d3f07b717504407614" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="1248681">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00018_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00018_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="3b9ab4366623f140a9dc0c23d75f5c5c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2022812">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00018_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="a720066b88ba854e5d49aa9a39f87eb0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2554176">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00019_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00019_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7f1154f5d07d60c6a11304fa2af10914" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2589118">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00019_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00020_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="5ca185a70270192eef115a4e5e48e38d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2593915">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00020_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00020_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="ae274539bc9498cd6e5533ef32c1ebe8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2429057">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000717_00020_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00018_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8641d6d5d86cbb59e5c69785f3e7eefa" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="8171">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00018_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00018_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="1c57cb65895bcfb6fae23ad13264e0b5" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57132">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00018_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00019_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="eb4571761459612f88ab419c0f89d907" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="94775">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00019_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00019_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e03eb8c7fbec794b8d3c981da8b4b1c3" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="103737">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00019_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00020_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="6cac7d12e658cbb5ab22bd2b552498ae" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="95674">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00020_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00020_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="0657b7e33d24918173b06308c5bea9d0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="64168">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000717_redacted_ALTO_00020_1.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0003" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" firstpage="13" lastpage="18">
              <court id="b35-4" pgmap="35">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division II</court>
              <docketnumber id="AT_" pgmap="35">CA 93-163</docketnumber>
              <citation id="AT1" pgmap="35">864 S.W.2d 875</citation>
              <parties id="b35-3" pgmap="35">Edward James SNISKY v. Sharon Kay WHISENHUNT</parties>
              <decisiondate id="b35-5" pgmap="35">Opinion delivered November 3, 1993</decisiondate>
              <judges id="b40-9" pgmap="40">Jennings, C.J., and Pittman, J., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys id="b36-6" pgmap="36">David Goldman, P.A., for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys id="b36-7" pgmap="36">Larry Honeycutt, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author id="b36-8" pgmap="36">Judith Rogers, Judge.</author>
                <p id="AGU" pgmap="36">The appellant, Edward James Snisky, appeals from an order of the Garland County Chancery Court in which he was found in contempt and which provided a period of visitation for the parties’ minor child with appellee, Sharon Kay Whisenhunt. On appeal, appellant raises two issues in which he contends that the chancery court lacked jurisdiction and thus committed error by both holding him in contempt and in grant­ing appellee visitation with the child. We disagree with appellant’s argument on the first point and affirm the finding of contempt; however, we agree with his second argument and reverse the order of visitation.</p>
                <p id="b36-9" pgmap="36(121) 37(33)">The record discloses that the parties in this case cohabitat-­ed for a time in the Bahamas and later in the State of Florida. On May 30, 1989, a male child was bom of this'unsolemnized union. Appellee thereafter left Florida with the child and returned to her home in Hot Springs, Arkansas. There, in the Garland Coun­ty Chancery Court, she initiated a paternity action against appel­lant. On February 4, 1991, a consent order was entered where­by appellant was recognized as the natural father of the child. As per their agreement, appellee was granted custody of the child, while appellant was given certain rights of visitation and was also required to pay child support. The agreed order further pro­vided that “[t]he parties have consented to the Court having both in person [sic] and in rem jurisdiction of this matter, as well as retaining such jurisdiction for any further Orders of Courts.”</p>
                <p id="b37-6" pgmap="37">It appears that the parties resolved their earlier differences with the result that appellee and the child moved back to Flori­da to live with appellant. The case file from the Garland Coun­ty Chancery Court contains a letter written by appellant’s coun­sel, dated June 13, 1991, informing the Court of the parties’ reconciliation and their agreement to abate the payment of child support. The letter also states that “[b]oth parties are aware that if the situation in Florida does not work to the benefit of all par­ties, that an action can be brought in Garland County for adju­dication of any new issues which may arise.”</p>
                <p id="b37-7" pgmap="37">After residing in Florida for roughly seven months, appellee again returned to Arkansas with the child. On April 9, 1992, shortly after appellee’s departure, appellant obtained an ex parte restraining order from the Circuit Court of Broward County, Flori­da, which prohibited appellee from removing the child from the county and granted temporary custody to appellant. It appears from the record that appellant obtained this emergency order based on his representations that appellee’s whereabouts were unknown and that the child was in danger due to appellee’s drug dependency. On April 15, 1992, appellee filed a petition in the Garland County Chancery Court seeking, among other things, the reinstatement of child support. Appellee further asked the chancery court to confirm custody of the child with her, to con­firm the court’s jurisdiction, and not to give the restraining order entered by the Florida court full faith and credit. On May 20, 1992, appellee also filed a motion asking that appellant be held in contempt, alleging that appellant’s institution of a custody action in Florida was a violation of their agreement contained in the court’s order of February 4, 1991, that custody matters be litigated in Arkansas.</p>
                <p id="b37-8" pgmap="37(68) 38(110)">After having the issue briefed, the chancellor declined to exercise jurisdiction over the matter of custody based on the find­ing that Florida had become the home state of the child under both the PKPA and UCCJA. An order to that effect was entered on May 27, 1992, and it appears that custody of the child was trans­ferred to appellant in accordance with the Florida court order. The case thereafter proceeded to a hearing on appellee’s motion for contempt. By order of August 23, 1992, the chancellor ruled that appellant was in contempt of the consent order for having brought a custody action in the Florida court. As a result, appel­lant was required to pay $4,526 into the registry of the court, plus $775 for costs. In addition, the chancellor ordered appel­lant to bring the child to Arkansas for visitation with appellee from July 4 to August 4, 1992. In the order, the chancellor also made a specific finding that appellant had misled the Florida court in securing the ex parte order. This appeal followed.</p>
                <p id="b38-4" pgmap="38">In this appeal, no questions are presented involving the inter­pretation of the provision in the consent order preserving juris­diction in the Arkansas Court. In other words, we are not asked to decide such issues as whether the jurisdictional provision of the agreed order was sufficiently definite and certain in its terms to support a finding of contempt,<footnotemark>1</footnotemark> or whether the provision con­stituted a valid forum selection clause as opposed to a simple retention of jurisdiction provision.<footnotemark>2</footnotemark> Indeed, in his response to appellee’s motion for contempt, appellant acknowledged that the order accurately reflected the parties’ agreement that Arkansas would remain the setting for future custody litigation. Instead, as his first point, it is appellant’s sole contention that the chancel­lor did not have jurisdiction over the contempt proceeding once jurisdiction of the custody matter was relinquished to the Flori­da Court. We do not agree.</p>
                <p id="b38-5" pgmap="38(42) 39(92)">
                   The chancellor here deferred to the Florida court’s exercise of jurisdiction over the issue of custody for the reason that Florida was the child’s home state under both the PKPA and UCCJA. This decision was based on evidence that the child had lived in Florida for the preceding seven months, as well as most of his young life. Despite the provision in the consent order, the chancellor acted well within his discretion in declining jurisdic­tion over the issue of custody. See Slusher v. Slusher, 31 Ark. App. 28, 786 S.W.2d 843 (1990); Ark. Code Ann. § 9-13-207 (1987). However, under the peculiar circumstances of this case, we do not view the chancellor’s decision to relinquish jurisdic­tion over the custody matter as having deprived the court of juris­diction over the contempt proceeding.</p>
                <p id="b39-6" pgmap="39(317) 40(14)">
                   The PKPA and UCCJA only specify circumstances under which a court has jurisdiction to make a “child custody determination.” Looking to the PKPA, “child custody determi­nation” is defined as a “judgment, decree, or other order of a court providing for the custody or visitation of a child, and includes permanent and temporary orders, and initial orders and modifications.” 28 U.S.C. § 1738A(b)(3) (1982) (emphasis sup­plied). The chancellor in this case simply declined to entertain jurisdiction of the pending custody determination, which involved the potential modification of the prior custody order. There is a distinction, however, between the modification of a custody deci­sion and the enforcement of a previous court order. When mod­ification of a previous custody order is at issue, the focus is on whether there has been a material change in circumstances and whether modification is in the best interest of the child. Bennett v. Hollowell, 31 Ark. App. 209, 792 S.W.2d 338 (1990). On the other hand, the subject of a contempt proceeding is whether the alleged contemnor willfully disobeyed a previous court order. See e.g. Dees v. Dees, 28 Ark. App. 108, 771 S.W.2d 299 (1989). In this instance, that portion of the order which the chancellor was asked to enforce through contempt did not involve any ques­tions relative to a custody determination, as that term has been defined. At issue was solely whether appellant’s actions were in violation of the agreed order. Since the question of appellant’s contempt did not touch upon the subject of child custody, juris­diction of the contempt proceeding was not governed by the PKPA. Therefore, the chancellor’s refusal of jurisdiction over the custody matter pursuant to the PKPA did not affect the chancery court’s inherent authority to enforce its order with regard to an issue unconnected with the custody determination. In sum, under these facts, we hold that the chancery court retained juris­diction over the issue of whether appellant was in contempt of the agreed order.</p>
                <p id="b40-6" pgmap="40">
                   As part of this first issue, appellant also contends that he cannot be held in contempt for taking advantage of the fed­eral statute by filing an action for modification in the child’s home state. While appellant’s pursuit of custody in Florida was in keeping with the PKPA, his actions were, nevertheless, in dis­regard of his agreement, which was incorporated as an order of the court, that Arkansas remain the forum for custody litigation. As the argument is presented, we can find no error in the chan­cellor’s determination that appellant not be allowed to disobey a court order with impunity.</p>
                <p id="b40-7" pgmap="40">
                   As his second issue, appellant argues that the chan­cellor lacked jurisdiction to grant appellee visitation rights with the child. We agree that the chancellor’s order of visitation was inconsistent with his decision favoring jurisdiction in the Flori­da court. As noted above, the definition of “custody determina­tion” in the PKPA does include orders providing for visitation with the child. Once the chancellor declined jurisdiction over the cus­tody determination, it follows that the chancery court no longer had jurisdiction to order a period of visitation. It is apparent that the chancellor’s action was prompted by appellant’s failure to bring the child to Arkansas for the hearing as appellant had assured the court he would do at a previous hearing. While the chancellor’s dismay is understandable, we cannot uphold the order of visitation. We must therefore reverse on this point.</p>
                <p id="b40-8" pgmap="40">Affirmed in part; reversed in part.</p>
                <footnote label="1">
                  <p id="b38-6" pgmap="38">1 The general rule is that before a person may be held in contempt for violating a court order, the order must be in definite terms as to the duties imposed upon him and the command must be expressed rather than implied. Arkansas Department of Human Services v. Gruber, 39 Ark. App. 112, 839 S.W.2d 543 (1992).</p>
                </footnote>
                <footnote label="2">
                  <p id="b38-7" pgmap="38">2 Choice of forum clauses in contracts have generally been held binding, unless it can be shown that the enforcement of the forum selection clause would be unreason­able and unfair. Nelms v. Morgan Portable Building Corp., 305 Ark. 284, 808 S.W.2d 314 (1991). For cases discussing such clauses in the context of custody litigation, see Crites v. Alston, 837 P.2d 1061 (Wyo. 1992); In re Marriage ofBeuche , 550 N.E.2d 48 (Ill. App. Ct. 1990); In re Marriage of Hilliard, 533 N.E.2d 543 (III. App. Ct. 1989).</p>
                </footnote>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="35" ORDERLABEL="13" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00018_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00018_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_35.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="36" ORDERLABEL="14" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00018_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00018_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_36.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="37" ORDERLABEL="15" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_37.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="38" ORDERLABEL="16" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00019_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00019_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_38.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="39" ORDERLABEL="17" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00020_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00020_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_39.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="40" ORDERLABEL="18" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00020_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00020_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_40.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AT_" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGU" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b35-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AT1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_35.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b36-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_36.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00018_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0003"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
