<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000704_0004" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="TEC v. Falkner">TEC and Commercial Union Insurance Companies v. Patsy FALKNER</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 91-211</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">38 Ark. App. 13</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">827 S.W.2d 661</citation>
          <decisiondate>1992-04-01</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-22T20:41:00Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T16:34:15Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:52:48Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-16T10:53:48Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="976afb564984604d226b190089ffd37b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="39962">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00019_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00019_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ce63d2c5575dcb2f8ef99b15a2cb8b6f" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="34808">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00019_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00020_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="a91a90449091eaec910b545609c350f8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54104">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00020_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00020_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="c2a43a3dcd4061a46f25919d75ab96e2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="52822">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00020_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00021_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="5972d856209efa4d603ebc141fd89ee0" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="54554">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00021_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00019_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="bc518bf09646b5b13746b3a40319d79c" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2571895">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00019_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00019_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6f491c9454d6902f80379aae59ae30ea" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2075599">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00019_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00020_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="626f698c79f88420f6cec2d93f3cf0a8" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2746551">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00020_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00020_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="7ddfe6958595744dbf1d8d24ee67dcfc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2672125">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00020_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00021_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="466b69a8efedbd5e648d31db30fb7e54" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2734466">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000704_00021_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00019_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="e9e5f2304080bc36743f30fee89c295a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="57903">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000704_redacted_ALTO_00019_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00019_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="8103f93fa11d754f8892cdd6fe4bc46a" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="50401">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000704_redacted_ALTO_00019_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00020_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="f94c40fff1333002c8c6162cb4b77b25" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="82386">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000704_redacted_ALTO_00020_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00020_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="9a7bce4d33b1c5e0faa2270b289e89e6" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="79814">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000704_redacted_ALTO_00020_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00021_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="fa4d4e2d7263974c14275462068b8d72" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="86811">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000704_redacted_ALTO_00021_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0004" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="17" firstpage="13">
              <court pgmap="37" id="b37-13">Court of Appeals of Arkansas En Banc</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="37" id="b37-12">CA 91-211</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="37" id="A_J">827 S.W.2d 661</citation>
              <parties pgmap="37" id="b37-10">TEC and Commercial Union Insurance Companies v. Patsy FALKNER</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="37" id="b37-14">Opinion delivered April 1, 1992</decisiondate>
              <otherdate pgmap="37" id="Al">[Rehearing denied July 8, 1992.]</otherdate>
              <judges pgmap="41" id="b41-7">Mayfield, J., dissents.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="38" id="b38-9">Daily, West, Core, Coffman, &amp; Canfield, by: Eldon F. Coffman and Douglas M. Carson, for appellants.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="38" id="b38-10">Bethell, Callaway, Robertson, &amp; Beasley, by: John R. Beasley, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="38" id="b38-11">George K. Cracraft, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="38" id="Am">TEC appeals from an order of the Arkansas Workers’ Compensation Commission and ad­vances several arguments. We dismiss the appeal because we conclude that the order appealed from is not final and appealable.</p>
                <p pgmap="38(144) 39(18)" id="b38-12">
                   Arkansas Code Annotated § 11-9-711(b)(2) (1987) provides that appeals from the Commission to this court shall be allowed as in other civil actions. For an order to be appealable, it must be final. To be final, an order must dismiss the parties from the court, discharge them from the action, or conclude their rights as to the subject matter in controversy. American Mutual Insurance Co. v. Argonaut Insurance Co., 33 Ark. App. 82, 801 S.W.2d 55 (1991); Samuels Hide and Metal Company v. Griffin, 23 Ark. App. 3, 739 S.W.2d 698 (1987). Ordinarily an order of the Commission is reviewable only at the point where it awards or denies compensation; interlocutory decisions and decisions on incidental matters are not reviewable for lack of finality. Stafford v. Diamond Construction Co., 31 Ark. App. 215, 793 S.W.2d 109 (1990); Mid-State Construction Company v. Sealy, 26 Ark. App. 186, 761 S.W.2d 951 (1988); Hernandez v. Simmons Industries, 25 Ark. App. 25, 752 S.W.2d 45 (1988).</p>
                <p pgmap="39" id="b39-6">The record before us reflects that appellee sustained a compensable injury in March 1989. Appellee did not select a physician, but was seen by eight physicians in several specialized fields of medicine. According to the Commission’s findings, the treatment had not appeared to resolve appellee’s difficulties, and the medical providers were not able to agree upon a diagnosis of the etiology of her difficulties, the need for future medical treatment, the type of treatment needed, if any, or the degree of any permanent partial disability she may have suffered as a result of her injuries.</p>
                <p pgmap="39" id="b39-7">Appellee filed a petition requesting that she be given an independent medical evaluation, and that her permanent partial disability be determined. At the hearing, she withdrew the request for an independent evaluation and substituted a petition in which she requested a change of physicians to Dr. Douglas Parker. By agreement of the parties, the issues to be litigated were limited to (1) the extent of any permanent disability that appellee may have suffered, (2) appellee’s entitlement to a change of physicians to Dr. Parker, and (3) attorneys’ fees.</p>
                <p pgmap="39" id="b39-8">Arkansas Statutes Annotated § ll-9-514(a)(l) (1987) provides in pertinent part as follows:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="39" id="b39-9">If the employer selects a physician, the claimant may petition the commission one (1) time only for a change of physician, and if the commission approves the change, with or without a hearing, the commission shall determine the second physician and shall not be found by recommenda­tions of claimant or respondent. However, if the change desired by the claimant is to a chiropractic physician, the claimant may make the change by giving advance written notification to the employer or carrier.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="39" id="b39-10">In his opinion, which the Commission adopted as its own, the administrative law judge stated:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="39(39) 40(26)" id="b39-11">After considering all of the evidence presented, it is my opinion that the [appellee] is entitled to a change of physicians under A.C.A. § 11-9-514, however, the unusual fact situation in this case makes it difficult for me to determine what type of specialist I should select or provide the [appellee] with any future reasonable and necessary treatment for her compensable injury. . . .</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="40" id="b40-6">Although the [appellee] has withdrawn her request for a medical evaluation, this Commission is vested by statute with discretionary authority to require such an examina­tion or evaluation not only at the request of one or more of the parties, but also on its own motion. It is my opinion that such an evaluation or examination is not only advisable, but is necessary, to determine the area of specialty or expertise of the physician who is to be selected by me to provide the [appellee] with further treatment for the compensable injury, if any such treatment is necessary. [Emphasis added].</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="40" id="b40-7">The administrative law judge directed that appellee undergo an evaluation by Dr. Marcia Hixson for her opinion as to (1) the type of medical specialist most likely to be qualified to provide appellee with any further reasonable and necessary medical treatment, if any, and (2) whether appellee had achieved maximum healing and, if so, the extent of her anatomical impairment, if any. See Ark. Code Ann. §§ 1 l-9-207(a)(l) and 1 l-9-508(a) (1987). The administrative law judge concluded as follows:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="40" id="b40-8">8. The [appellee] is entitled to a change of physicians pursuant to A. C. A. § 11-9-514, however, a selection of the appropriate physician to provide [appellee] with any further reasonable and necessary medical treatment for the compensable injury, if such is required, is reserved pending receipt of the evaluation of the [appellee] by Dr. Hixson.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="40" id="b40-9">9. The issue of the existence and extent of permanent disability resulting from the compensable injury, attribu­table to both anatomical impairment and functional disa­bility, is reserved for further determination following the ordered evaluation by Dr. Marcia Hixson and pending receipt of her findings. [Emphasis added].</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="40(28) 41(51)" id="b40-10">
                   Neither appellee’s petition for a change of physicians nor the extent of her permanent disability was finally determined. They were reserved for further action by the Commission upon the receipt of the report of Dr. Hixson. As such, the Commission’s order was interlocutory in nature, and the Commission’s direc­tions that appellant pay Dr. Hixson a fee for the evaluation and pay appellee an attorney’s fee for the change of physicians yet to be determined were merely incidental thereto.</p>
                <p pgmap="41" id="b41-6">Dismissed.</p>
                <author pgmap="41" id="b41-8">Melvin Mayfield, Judge,</author>
                <p pgmap="41" id="AAK">dissenting. This is another chapter in the continuing saga of the search for the appealable order in workers’ compensation cases. The need for an agreement upon what constitutes a final, appealable order in these cases becomes clearly evident upon a reading of the majority, concur­ring, and dissenting opinions in Hampton and Crain v. Black, 34 Ark. App. 77, 806 S.W.2d 21 (1991). That confusion reigns is demonstrated by the fact that each of those opinions rely, to some extent, on the case of Gina Marie Farms v. Jones, 28 Ark. App. 90, 770 S.W.2d 680 (1989). However, like the blind men examining the elephant, each opinion exhibits a different concept of the matter examined.</p>
                <p pgmap="41" id="b41-9">The concept of the majority in the instant case is especially at variance with Gina Marie Farms which recognized the appeala-­bility of an order which ends a “separable branch” of the litigation. In the instant case, a number of issues were presented to the administrative law judge. One issue was whether the appellee should have a change of physicians. The law judge thought the appellee needed a change and it was the judge’s duty to choose a new physician. Since he did not know which one to choose, he thought it “not only advisable but necessary” to have appellee evaluated by a doctor who could tell the law judge the “area of specialty or expertise of the physician” that the law judge should approve for further treatment, if necessary, of the claim­ant. I cannot understand why the law judge’s order, affirmed by the Commission, directing appellee to undergo such an evalua­tion did not end a separable branch'of the litigation and was not appealable. See my dissenting opinion in Stafford v. Diamond Construction Co., 31 Ark. App. 215, 793 S.W.2d 109 (1990).</p>
                <p pgmap="41" id="b41-10">I dissent from the majority decision dismissing this appeal.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="37" ORDERLABEL="13" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00019_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_37.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="38" ORDERLABEL="14" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00019_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00019_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_38.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="39" ORDERLABEL="15" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00020_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00020_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_39.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="40" ORDERLABEL="16" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00020_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00020_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_40.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="41" ORDERLABEL="17" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00021_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00021_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_41.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AAK" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b38-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A_J" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b37-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b41-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b40-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_40.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Am" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_38.13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Al" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_37.14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00019_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b41-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b41-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b39-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_39.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00020_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b41-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b41-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0004"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_41.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00021_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
