<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<mets xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" xmlns="http://www.loc.gov/METS/">
  <dmdSec ID="case">
    <mdWrap MDTYPE="OTHER" OTHERMDTYPE="HLS-CASELAW-CASEXML">
      <xmlData>
        <case xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case:v1" caseid="NOTALEPH000652_0024" publicationstatus="published">
          <court abbreviation="Ark. Ct. App." jurisdiction="Arkansas">Arkansas Court of Appeals</court>
          <name abbreviation="Liberty Life Insurance Co. v. Forsythe">LIBERTY LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY v. Martha FORSYTHE</name>
          <docketnumber>CA 87-437</docketnumber>
          <citation category="official" type="bluebook">25 Ark. App. 147</citation>
          <citation category="parallel" type="bluebook">752 S.W.2d 305</citation>
          <decisiondate>1988-07-06</decisiondate>
        </case>
      </xmlData>
    </mdWrap>
  </dmdSec>
  <amdSec ID="amd0001">
    <digiprovMD ID="digi001">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>scn0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>capture</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2016-03-21T22:16:37Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Scan date noting when printed source volume was converted to digital images used as sources for transcription.</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>HLSL</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Harvard Law School Library</agentName>
            <agentType>organization</agentType>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi002">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>ocr0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>transcription</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-06-27T15:22:51Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Transcription event</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>dsrs</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata DSRS, ABBYY FineReader</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 10</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi003">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>crt0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>METScreation</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-18T15:33:24Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Creation of digital artifact described by this METS file</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redrli</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
    <digiprovMD ID="digi004">
      <mdWrap MDTYPE="PREMIS">
        <xmlData>
          <event xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <eventIdentifier>
              <eventIdentifierType>Local</eventIdentifierType>
              <eventIdentifierValue>red0001</eventIdentifierValue>
            </eventIdentifier>
            <eventType>redaction</eventType>
            <eventDateTime>2017-07-18T15:35:19Z</eventDateTime>
            <eventDetail>Redaction step</eventDetail>
          </event>
          <agent xmlns="info:lc/xmlns/premis-v2">
            <agentIdentifier>
              <agentIdentifierType>Local</agentIdentifierType>
              <agentIdentifierValue>redravel-redactor</agentIdentifierValue>
            </agentIdentifier>
            <agentName>Innodata R.E.D. Workbench/RLI tool</agentName>
            <agentType>software</agentType>
            <agentNote>Version 20170713.post178</agentNote>
          </agent>
        </xmlData>
      </mdWrap>
    </digiprovMD>
  </amdSec>
  <fileSec>
    <fileGrp USE="tiff">
      <file ID="tiff_00088_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="fa499f749bab337ee75a0bf12a0cefcc" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="26400">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00088_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00088_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="06aba89101e774ec45f4fa9793d75f99" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="48514">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00088_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00089_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="ca1ed9d751014c60b8d603f6d7ac6abb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="52396">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00089_0.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00089_1" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="825173b56a2c7ee852c98d15a1321e91" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="49112">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00089_1.tif"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="tiff_00090_0" MIMETYPE="image/tiff" CHECKSUM="e77ac8ddad18f15dfa19bd8bd2e8919b" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="42910">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00090_0.tif"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="jp2">
      <file ID="jp2_00088_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="eb6159e97ac33e37046e0c4263df8093" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2074319">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00088_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00088_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="87903769743444d7faff60bc53e6a78d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2543043">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00088_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00089_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="06600f5c49ccf2551903baaf01a79343" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2626068">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00089_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00089_1" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="3d8c25e5bc6baa3a9f12f8ecb07fb8e2" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2610281">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00089_1.jp2"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="jp2_00090_0" MIMETYPE="image/jp2" CHECKSUM="6677dacc3823e98de6ad6ed114c5e260" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="2545389">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../images/NOTALEPH000652_00090_0.jp2"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="alto">
      <file ID="alto_00088_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="a2a0a872b65f4a3aab88d8264091b9ed" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="37137">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000652_redacted_ALTO_00088_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00088_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="241ac81dc87e6a165e97e48ec9c5eecb" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="79427">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000652_redacted_ALTO_00088_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00089_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="d25a189e17ee242d4b2895e82e8a362d" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="82383">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000652_redacted_ALTO_00089_0.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00089_1" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="c69fe94af6cd741ff07948e1d7b04b34" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="72542">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000652_redacted_ALTO_00089_1.xml"/>
      </file>
      <file ID="alto_00090_0" MIMETYPE="text/xml" CHECKSUM="3b95b63edd38586d1f4d14db03d676e4" CHECKSUMTYPE="MD5" SIZE="64702">
        <FLocat LOCTYPE="URL" xlink:href="../alto/NOTALEPH000652_redacted_ALTO_00090_0.xml"/>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
    <fileGrp USE="casebody">
      <file ID="casebody_0024" MIMETYPE="text/xml">
        <FContent>
          <xmlData>
            <casebody xmlns="http://nrs.harvard.edu/urn-3:HLS.Libr.US_Case_Law.Schema.Case_Body:v1" lastpage="151" firstpage="147">
              <court pgmap="175" id="Azl">Court of Appeals of Arkansas Division I</court>
              <docketnumber pgmap="175" id="AsqF">CA 87-437</docketnumber>
              <citation pgmap="175" id="A4p">752 S.W.2d 305</citation>
              <parties pgmap="175" id="b175-6">LIBERTY LIFE INSURANCE COMPANY v. Martha FORSYTHE</parties>
              <decisiondate pgmap="175" id="Apo">Opinion delivered July 6, 1988</decisiondate>
              <judges pgmap="179" id="b179-9">Cooper and Jennings, JJ., agree.</judges>
              <attorneys pgmap="175" id="b175-12">Barrett, Wheatley, Smith &amp; Deacon, for appellant.</attorneys>
              <attorneys pgmap="175" id="b175-13">Henry, Walden &amp; Davis, for appellee.</attorneys>
              <opinion type="majority">
                <author pgmap="175" id="b175-14">Melvin Mayfield, Judge.</author>
                <p pgmap="175(63) 176(32)" id="AGY">This appeal results from the trial court’s entry of a default judgment against appellant, Liberty Life Insurance Company. Appellant raises three points for reversal: (1) the default judgment should be set aside because a defective summons was served upon appellant and appellant has a meritorious defense to the complaint; (2) the answer of codefendant Insurex Agency, Inc. inures to the benefit of appel­lant; and (3) just cause existed for appellant’s failure to file a timely answer. Because we find that codefendant Insurex’s answer did plead a defense common to appellant, we reverse and remand.</p>
                <p pgmap="176" id="b176-6">The appellee filed suit against the appellant alleging that she was the beneficiary in a certificate issued by appellant, pursuant to its group insurance policy, insuring the life of appellee’s deceased husband. Appellee alleged that she should have judg­ment against appellant for the amount provided by the certificate and, in the alternative, judgment against the codefendant In-­surex. The issue presented in this case is whether the answer filed by the codefendant asserted a defense common to appellant and went to the merits of the whole cause of action. In Firestone Tire &amp; Rubber Co. v. Little, 269 Ark. 636, 599 S.W.2d 756 (Ark. App. 1980), we said:</p>
                <p pgmap="176" id="b176-7">In 78 A.L.R. 939 is found a statement as follows:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="176" id="b176-8">The courts are agreed with practical unanimity that in actions against several defendants jointly, where the defense interposed by the answering defendant is not personal to himself (as is the defense of infancy, coverture, or bankruptcy on the part of the pleader), but common to all, as where it goes to the whole right of the plaintiff to recover at all, as distinguished from his right to recover as against any particular defendant, or questions the merits or validity of the plaintiffs entire cause of action in general, or his right to sue, such defense, if successful, inures to the benefit of the defaulting defendants both in actions at law and suits in equity, with the result that final judgment must be entered not merely in favor of the answering defend­ant, but also in favor of the defaulting defendants.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="176" id="b176-9">In71 C.J.S., Pleadings, Section 117, at p. 268isfound the statement as follows:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="176(31) 177(24)" id="b176-10">While as a general rule one defendant cannot in his answer assert the rights of a codefendant who does not answer, a defense which goes to the merits of the whole case as tending to show no cause of action in plaintiff may, when pleaded by one defendant, inure to the benefit of his codefendants.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="177" id="b177-5">It is not every answer filed by a defendant that inures to the benefit of a nonanswering codefendant. It is only when the answering defendant answers an allegation directed at and common to his nonanswering codefendant. The purpose and effect of an answer by general denial is to put the plaintiff to proof on each of the allegations made in the complaint.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="177" id="b177-6">269 Ark. at 642-3.</p>
                <p pgmap="177" id="b177-7">In Arkansas Electric Co. v. Cone-Huddleston, 249 Ark. 230, 458 S.W.2d 728 (1970), the Arkansas Supreme Court stated, “Commercial [non-answering defendant] timely re­quested its insured, Cone-Huddleston, to file an answer in the former’s behalf and to defend, as it was contractually obligated to do. Of course the defenses would be identical and Commercial Union’s liability would be predicated on Cone-Huddleston being liable.” 249 Ark. at 231. In Southland Mobile Home Corp. v. Winders, 262 Ark. 693, 561 S.W.2d 280 (1978), however, the Arkansas Supreme Court distinguished its holding in Arkansas Electric.</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="177" id="b177-8">The appellees are mistaken in arguing, on the basis of the result reached in Rogers v. Watkins, 258 Ark. 394, 525 S.W.2d 665 (1975), that there must be a derivative liability in order for the answer of one defendant to inure to the benefit of another. That was the situation in Rogers, but the rule is not confined to that state of facts. The true test is whether the answer of the non-defaulting defendant states a defense that is common to both defendants, because then a “successful plea .... operates as a discharge to all the defendants but it is otherwise where the plea goes to the personal discharge of the party interposing it.” [Citations omitted] Here the effect of the manufac­turer’s answer was to deny the plaintiffs’ allegations of negligence and breach of warranty. That denial went to the existence of the plaintiffs’ cause of action, asserted a defense common to both defendants, and therefore inured to the benefit of the appellant.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-5">262 Ark. at 694.</p>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-6">In Allied Chemical Corp. v. Van Buren School District No. 42, 264 Ark. 810, 575 S.W.2d 445 (1979), the appellants argued that codefendant Celotex’s timely answer brought their case within the rule that any defense filed by one defendant, common to a codefendant, inured to their benefit. The Arkansas Supreme Court responded:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="178" id="b178-7">Here Celotex filed a timely answer, preserving its objection to venue, and asserted that the appellees’ com­plaint did not state sufficient facts to constitute a cause of action, denied the allegations of appellee’s complaint, interposed the statute of limitations as a complete defense .... These denials by Celotex’s answers went to the existence of appellee’s cause of action and asserted de­fenses common to both appellants which inured to their benefit.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-8">264 Ark. at 815.</p>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-9">In the present case, the appellee alleged separate causes of action against appellant and defendant Insurex. The allegation as to defendant Insurex is that it misrepresented the fact that appellee’s husband would be covered under his employer’s group policy with appellant. The appellee did not allege joint and several liability as to Insurex and appellant but asked for relief against Insurex, if appellee was not successful on her claim against appellant.</p>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-10">Appellee’s specific claim against appellant is based upon waiver and estoppel. In paragraph 11 of her amended complaint, appellee specifically alleges:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="178" id="b178-11">That [appellant], Liberty Life Insurance Company, by their actions in accepting premiums for the life insur­ance coverage on Robert Lewis Forsythe [appellee’s hus­band], as well as the medical care coverage, and also in honoring all claims for medical care coverage under the policy, should be found to have waived any right to deny coverage under the policy, and should be stopped [sic] from denying coverage under same.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="178" id="b178-12">In response to this allegation, defendant Insurex answered,</p>
                <p pgmap="179" id="b179-4">“[t]his defendant can neither admit nor deny the allegations contained in Paragraph 11 of the Amended Complaint, as said allegations are directed toward Liberty Life Insurance Company, but this defendant would demand strict proof of said allegations if its rights are to be affected.” Thus, defendant Insurex did not answer for appellant. Nevertheless in paragraphs 16 &amp; 17 of its answer, defendant Insurex further pleads:</p>
                <blockquote pgmap="179" id="b179-5">For further defense, the defendant, Insurex Agency, Inc., alleges that the [appellee] is barred from recovery in this case on the ground that Richard Lewis Forsythe specifically misrepresented his employment status in Feb­ruary of 1985 by stating that he worked a minimum of thirty hours per week and that he was an active, full-time employee, all of which induced Liberty Life Insurance Company to show him as an insured. . . . This defendant avers that the plaintiff is barred from recovery on the basis of the misrepresentation of Richard Lewis Forsythe, which representations void any coverages to which he or his beneficiary might otherwise be entitled.</blockquote>
                <blockquote pgmap="179" id="b179-6">17. The plaintiff is estopped to claim the benefits of life insurance coverage on the life of Richard Lewis Forsythe because of the above-described misrepresenta­tions as to the work status of Richard Lewis Forsythe.</blockquote>
                <p pgmap="179" id="b179-7">
                   Thus, we think it clear that the defenses of misrepresen­tation of employment status and estoppel pled by Insurex were defenses common to Insurex and appellant, Liberty Life. There­fore, the timely answer of Insurex inures to the benefit of Liberty Life, and it was error to enter default judgment against appellant.</p>
                <p pgmap="179" id="b179-8">Reversed and remanded.</p>
              </opinion>
            </casebody>
          </xmlData>
        </FContent>
      </file>
    </fileGrp>
  </fileSec>
  <structMap TYPE="physical">
    <div TYPE="volume">
      <div ORDER="175" ORDERLABEL="147" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00088_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00088_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_175.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="176" ORDERLABEL="148" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00088_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00088_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_176.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="177" ORDERLABEL="149" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00089_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00089_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_177.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="178" ORDERLABEL="150" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00089_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00089_1"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_178.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
      <div ORDER="179" ORDERLABEL="151" TYPE="page">
        <fptr FILEID="tiff_00090_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="jp2_00090_0"/>
        <fptr FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
        <div TYPE="pagelabel">
          <fptr>
            <seq>
              <area BEGIN="BL_179.2" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
            </seq>
          </fptr>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
  <structMap TYPE="xref">
    <div TYPE="blocks">
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b176-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_177.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b177-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_177.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AGY" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.18" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.19" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.1" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="AsqF" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b176-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b175-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.15" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b175-13" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.16" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b175-14" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.17" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b177-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_177.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b177-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_177.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b177-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_177.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Azl" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b176-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b175-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b176-7" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.5" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b176-6" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_176.4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b179-4" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_179.3" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00090_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="A4p" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="Apo" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_175.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00088_0"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-11" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.9" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.8" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
      <div TYPE="element">
        <fptr>
          <area BEGIN="b178-12" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="casebody_0024"/>
        </fptr>
        <fptr>
          <seq>
            <area BEGIN="BL_178.10" BETYPE="IDREF" FILEID="alto_00089_1"/>
          </seq>
        </fptr>
      </div>
    </div>
  </structMap>
</mets>
